<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ZenMom</string>
    <string name="heading">ZenMom</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to <font size="18"><b>ZenMom</b></font>\nYour Trusted Companion on the Journey of Motherhood. Embrace the Experience!</string>
    <string name="allRightReserved">©LamuSoft 2024</string>
    <string name="shareMessage">🌟 Exciting News for Moms-to-Be! Welcome to ZenMom: Your Ultimate Pregnancy Companion! 🤰\n\nExplore a realm of realistic guidelines, baby growth milestones, and a supportive community, all tailored to make your pregnancy journey magical. 🌟👶 Download now to effortlessly embrace the joy of pregnancy!\n #ZenMom #PregnancyJoy #MomToBe 💖\n\nCurious to experience the magic? Dive in now! 🚀\n</string>

    <string name="about">About Us</string>

    <string name="ad">Advertising</string>

    <string name="medicalDisclaimer"><b>Content Disclaimer:</b>\nThis app does not provide medical advice. Content is for informational purposes only and does not replace professional consultation. Always consult a qualified healthcare provider for medical guidance. If you have a medical emergency, call your doctor or emergency services. We do not endorse specific treatments or practitioners. Reliance on app content is at your own risk. Developers are not liable for decisions based on the app.
        \n\n</string>

    <string name="babyGrowthTitle">Baby Growth</string>
    <string name="nutritionTitle">Nutrition Tips</string>
    <string name="partnerSupport">Partner Roles</string>
    <string name="babySIzeTitle">Baby Size</string>
    <string name="motherHealthTitle">Mother Health</string>
    <string name="guideTitle">Womb Wellness hub</string>
    <string name="testKitGuide">Explore Testing Kit…</string>
    <string name="BMI">BMI Calculator</string>
    <string name="more">More…</string>
    <string name="coming">Dear Valued <b>ZenMom</b> Users,\n\n<b>Greetings!</b> We are thrilled to inform you that our development team is diligently working on introducing new and enhanced features to elevate your experience with the app. The upcoming changes are currently in the development phase and will be unveiled shortly.\nYour patience is highly appreciated as we strive to deliver a seamless and enriched app environment. Should you have any feedback or suggestions, we are more than eager to hear from you.\n\nThank you for your continued support.\n\nBest Regards,\n<b>ZenMom Developer Team.</b></string>
    <string name="HomeMade">Homemade Test</string>
    <string name="Urine">Urine Test</string>
    <string name="Signs">Signs and Symptoms</string>
    <string name="shareTitle">Share</string>

    <!--Prenatal Nutrition-->
    <string name="prenatalNutritionHeading">Secrets of Prenatal Nutrition for a Healthy Pregnancy</string>
    <string name="pd1">Pregnant? Get nutrition tips for a healthy baby! Our guide covers key nutrients like folic acid and omega-3 fatty acids. Learn their importance, sources, and practical meal tips. Empower yourself with info on cravings, portion sizes, and more. Nourish yourself and your baby with our prenatal nutrition journey!\n</string>

    <string name="pd2h"><b>✤ Importance of Prenatal Nutrition</b></string>
    <string name="pd2">Eating well when pregnant is important for the mother and the unborn child. It lowers the chance of infant abnormalities, encourages growth, and guarantees a safe pregnancy. The baby \'s organs receive essential nutrients from a balanced diet. Pregnancy problems are avoided by having higher nutrient requirements. Give prenatal nutrition a top priority for long-term health. Determine the precise nutrients required for a diet to be successful.\n</string>

    <string name="pd3h"><b>✤ Nutritional Needs During Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="pd3">More nutrients throughout pregnancy are essential for the growth of your unborn child. This comprises micronutrients (minerals and vitamins) and macronutrients (carbs, protein, and healthy fats).\n<b>- Carbs: </b>For consistent energy and fiber, go for fruits, vegetables, and whole grains.\n<b>- Protein: </b>Required for the formation of tissue. Add fish, beans, dairy, and lean meats.\n<b>- Healthy Fats:</b> Omega-3s support the development of a baby \'s brain and eyes. Fish, avocados, almonds, and seeds all contain them.\n<b>Minerals and Vitamins:</b> vital to prenatal growth and body processes. Pay attention to calcium, vitamin D, iron, and folic acid. There are in-depth talks about these nutrients after this.</string>

    <string name="pd4h"><b>✤ How Many Calories Do You Need During Pregnancy?</b></string>
    <string name="pd4">Contrary to the popular myth of "eating for two, you don \'t need to double your calorie intake during pregnancy. Gradually increasing your calorie intake as your baby develops is sufficient. On average, you should aim for around 2,200–2,500 calories per day. However, individual calorie needs may vary based on factors such as pre-pregnancy weight, activity level, and multiple pregnancies.\n</string>

    <string name="pd5h"><b>✤ Weight Gain During Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="pd5">Gaining weight is a normal and essential aspect of the process during pregnancy. It helps the placenta, amniotic fluid, your baby \'s growth and development, and other vital structures. The suggested weight increase varies based on your body mass index (BMI) before pregnancy:\n</string>

    <string name="pd6">\nIt \'s important to note that these are general guidelines, and you should consult with your healthcare provider for personalized recommendations.</string>

    <string name="p7h">\n<b>Foods to Avoid During Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="p7">It \'s crucial to know what to include in your pregnancy diet as well as what to avoid. Avoid:\n<b>• Uncooked or raw shellfish and meats:</b> They might have dangerous germs or parasites in them, which could cause problems or food poisoning.\n<b>• Uncooked eggs:</b> Eggs should be cooked until the whites and yolks are solid to help prevent salmonella.\n<b>• Non-pasteurized dairy items:</b> Raw milk and cheeses increase the risk of infection by containing bacteria like listeria.\n<b>• Fish high in mercury:</b> Fish that are hazardous to a developing baby \'s nervous system include swordfish and sharks. Select low-mercury substitutes.\n<b>• Drinking and caffeine:</b> You should stay away from both. While excessive caffeine may raise the risk of miscarriage and low birth weight, alcohol can cause developmental problems.</string>

    <string name="p8h"><b>✤ Meal Planning for Prenatal Nutrition</b></string>
    <string name="p8">Making a plan for your meals will help guarantee that you get the nourishment you need while pregnant. The following advice will assist you in developing a nutritious and well-balanced food plan:\n<b>• Consume a range of foods:</b> Your meals should contain a variety of fruits, vegetables, nutritious grains, lean meats, and healthy fats. This will assist you in obtaining a wide range of nutrients.\n<b>• Pay attention to nutrient-dense food:</b> Pick foods high in nutrients, such as plant-based proteins, whole grains, colorful fruits and vegetables, lean meats, and leafy greens. Pay attention to your body. Observe your body \'s signals of hunger and fullness. When you are hungry, eat, and when you are full, stop. Don \'t cut calories because your body needs more energy when you \'re pregnant.\n<b>• Eat more often and in smaller portions:</b> Eating more often and in smaller portions throughout the day can help ease common pregnant discomforts like heartburn and nausea.\n<b>• Stay hydrated: </b> To promote healthy digestion, hydration, and general well-being, sip lots of water throughout the day.
    </string>

    <string name="p8d">Remember, each pregnancy is unique, and it \'s essential to consult with your healthcare provider or a registered dietitian for personalized guidance and meal-planning advice.\n</string>
    <string name="p9h"><b>✤ Supplements for Prenatal Nutrition</b></string>
    <string name="p9">Most vital nutrients should be found in a well-balanced diet, but some pregnant women might need to take extra supplements. Prenatal vitamins are designed specifically to fulfill the heightened dietary requirements of expecting moms. Iron, calcium, vitamin D, folic acid, and other vital vitamins and minerals are usually present. You must speak with your healthcare professional before beginning any supplement regimen, though. They can evaluate your particular requirements and suggest the right kind and quantity of prenatal supplements for you.\n
    </string>
    <string name="p10h"><b>✤ Common Nutritional Deficiencies During Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="p10">Despite your best efforts, it \'s possible to experience nutritional deficiencies during pregnancy. Some common deficiencies include:\n
     • <b>Iron deficiency:</b> Iron deficiency anemia is common during pregnancy due to increased blood volume. If you \'re experiencing fatigue, weakness, or shortness of breath, your healthcare provider may recommend iron supplementation.\n
     • <b>Calcium deficiency:</b> Inadequate calcium intake can lead to weakened bones and teeth. Your healthcare provider may suggest calcium supplements if your diet falls short.\n
     • <b>Vitamin D deficiency:</b> Many individuals have insufficient vitamin D levels, especially during winter months or if they have limited sun exposure. Vitamin D supplementation may be necessary to ensure optimal levels.\n
        \nRegular check-ups and blood tests can help identify and address any nutritional deficiencies you may have. Always consult with your healthcare provider to determine the best course of action.\n
    </string>
    <string name="p11h"><b>✤ Tips for Maintaining a Healthy Diet During Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="p11">Maintaining a healthy diet during pregnancy doesn \'t have to be overwhelming. Here are some practical tips to support your journey:\n
    • <b>Plan your meals and snacks:</b> Prepare a weekly meal plan and grocery list to ensure you have nutritious options readily available. This can help you resist the temptation of unhealthy choices.\n
    • <b>Stock up on healthy snacks:</b> Keep a variety of healthy snacks on hand, such as fresh fruits, cut vegetables, nuts, and yogurt. These can help satisfy cravings and provide essential nutrients.\n
    • <b>Listen to your cravings:</b> While it \'s important to prioritize nutritious foods, it \'s also okay to indulge in the occasional craving. Just remember to do so in moderation and opt for healthier alternatives when possible.\n
    • <b>Stay active:</b>Regular physical activity during pregnancy can help manage weight gain, boost mood, and improve overall well-being. Engage in activities approved by your healthcare provider, such as walking, swimming, or prenatal yoga.\n
    • <b>Seek support:</b> Connect with other expectant mothers or join pregnancy support groups to share experiences, recipes, and tips. Having a support system can make the journey more enjoyable and less stressful.\n
    </string>
    <string name="p12h"><b>✤ Essential Nutrients for a Healthy Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="p12">
    • <b>Folic Acid:</b> Folic acid, also known as folate, is a B vitamin that plays a vital role in the formation of the baby \'s neural tube, which develops into the brain and spinal cord. Lack of folic acid can lead to neural tube defects. Ensure you consume foods rich in folic acid such as leafy green vegetables, citrus fruits, beans, and fortified grains.\n
    • <b>Iron:</b> Iron is necessary for the production of red blood cells, which carry oxygen to your body and your baby. During pregnancy, your blood volume increases, requiring more iron. Incorporate iron-rich foods like lean meats, poultry, fish, legumes, and fortified cereals. Pairing iron-rich foods with vitamin C enhances iron absorption.\n
    • <b>Calcium:</b> Calcium is essential for the development of your baby \'s bones, teeth, and muscles. If your diet lacks calcium, your body will draw from your bones to meet the baby \'s needs, potentially leading to weakened bones. Consume dairy products, fortified plant-based alternatives, leafy greens, and calcium-fortified foods to ensure an adequate intake.\n
    • <b>Vitamin D:</b> Vitamin D works together with calcium to support bone health. It also plays a role in the immune system and overall well-being. Exposure to sunlight triggers vitamin D synthesis in the body. Additionally, include foods like fatty fish, eggs, and fortified dairy products in your diet.\n
    • <b>Omega-3 Fatty Acids:</b> Omega-3 fatty acids, specifically DHA (docosahexaenoic acid), are crucial for the development of the baby \'s brain and eyes. Include fatty fish (salmon, sardines), walnuts, chia seeds, and flaxseeds in your diet to ensure an adequate intake of these beneficial fats.\n
    </string>
    <string name="p13h"><b>✤ Recipes for Prenatal Nutrition</b></string>
    <string name="p13">
        To help you incorporate essential nutrients into your diet, here are a couple of simple and nutritious recipes:\n
    • <b>Spinach and Feta Stuffed Chicken Breast:</b>\n
        <b><i>Ingredients:</i></b> \n
        1. 2 boneless, skinless chicken breasts.\n
        2. 1 cup fresh chopped spinach.\n
        3. 1/4 cup crumbled feta cheese.\n
        4. 1 minced garlic clove.\n
        5. Salt and pepper to taste\n\n
        <b><i>Instructions: </i></b>\n
        1. Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).\n
        2. Cut a pocket into each chicken breast, being careful not to cut through.\n
        3. In a bowl, combine spinach, feta cheese, garlic, salt, and pepper.\n
        4. Stuff each chicken breast with the spinach and feta mixture.\n
        5. Place the stuffed chicken breasts on a baking sheet and bake for 25-30 minutes or until cooked through.\n
        6. Serve with roasted vegetables or a salad.\n\n
     • <b>Berry and Greek Yogurt Parfait: </b>\n
        <b><i>Ingredients:</i></b>\n
        1. 1 cup Greek yogurt.\n
        2. 1/2 cup mixed berries (strawberries, blueberries, raspberries).\n
        3. 2 tablespoons honey.\n
        4. 1/4 cup granola.\n\n
        <b><i>Instructions:</i></b>\n
        1. In a glass or bowl, layer Greek yogurt, mixed berries, honey, and granola.\n
        2. Repeat the layers until all ingredients are used.\n
        4. Enjoy it as a nutritious breakfast or snack.\n\n
        Feel free to modify these recipes based on your preferences and dietary restrictions.\n
    </string>
    <string name="p14h"><b>✤ Conclusion: Taking Care of Your Nutritional Needs During Pregnancy</b>
    </string>
    <string name="p14">Ensuring proper nutrition during pregnancy is essential for the health and development of both you and your baby. By understanding the importance of prenatal nutrition, incorporating essential nutrients into your meals, avoiding harmful foods, and seeking personalized guidance, you can create a well-balanced diet that supports a healthy pregnancy.\nRemember to listen to your body, stay hydrated, and practice self-care throughout your pregnancy journey. Celebrate the joy of nurturing your baby through nutritious meals and embrace the excitement of this incredible chapter in your life.\nAs always, consult with your healthcare provider or a registered dietitian for specific recommendations and personalized advice. Wishing you a healthy and vibrant pregnancy!\n
    </string>

    <string name="sl1"><b>American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists (ACOG):</b>\nWebsite: https://www.acog.org/womens-health/faqs/nutrition-during-pregnancy
    </string>
    <string name="sl2"><b>Health.gov - MyHealthFinder:</b>\nWebsite: https://health.gov/myhealthfinder/pregnancy/nutrition-and-physical-activity/eat-healthy-during-pregnancy-quick-tips
    </string>
    <string name="sl3"><b>Johns Hopkins Medicine:</b>\nWebsite: https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/wellness-and-prevention/nutrition-during-pregnancy
    </string>
    <string name="sl4"><b>University of Michigan Medicine - Patient and Family Support Services:</b>\nWebsite: https://www.med.umich.edu/pfans/_pdf/hetm-2017/0417-prenatalnutrition.pdf
    </string>
    <string name="sl5"><b>Nutrition.gov:</b>\nWebsite: https://www.nutrition.gov/topics/nutrition-life-stage/pregnancy
    </string>

    <string name="prenatalNutritionDesclaimer"><b>Disclaimer:</b>The information is for general informational purposes. Sources include ACOG, health.gov, Johns Hopkins Medicine, the University of Michigan, and nutrition.gov. Consult healthcare professionals for personalized advice. The author, Rakibul Islam Mehedi, and sources don \'t endorse specific products. Verify the information and seek guidance from healthcare providers. External sources \' inclusion doesn \'t guarantee accuracy. The guide may not cover every aspect, and new research may have emerged. Consult healthcare providers for personalized advice on caloric intake, weight gain, foods to avoid, and supplements. Individual pregnancies vary; seek support from professionals and pregnancy groups. Always consult healthcare providers for personalized medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment.\n\nregards.
</string>

    <!--Folic Acid-->
    <string name="folicAcidHeading">Unlocking the Power of Folic Acid: A Crucial Element for Every Woman \'s Health</string>
    <string name="f">Folic acid is a crucial nutrient that offers lifelong benefits for women, extending beyond its association with pregnancy. This article delves into the significance of folic acid, its advantages for women of all ages, and strategies for integrating it into daily routines.\n
    </string>
    <string name="fh1"><b>✤ Understanding Folic Acid</b>
    </string>
    <string name="f1">Folic acid, the synthetic form of folate or vitamin B9, plays a pivotal role in various bodily functions, including DNA replication, prevention of birth defects, and red blood cell production. While folate can be obtained from certain foods, folic acid, found in supplements and enriched foods, ensures optimal levels of vitamin B9.\n
    </string>
    <string name="fh2"><b>✤ Benefits of Folic Acid for Women</b>
    </string>
    <string name="f2"><b>Preventing Birth Defects and Pregnancy-Related Complications</b>\nFolic acid significantly reduces the risk of neural tube defects (NTDs) in babies, such as anencephaly and spina bifida, when taken before and during pregnancy.\n\n<b>Avoiding Folate Deficiency Symptoms</b>\nFolate deficiency can lead to anemia, weakness, and fatigue due to its role in red blood cell production.\n\n<b>Promoting Brain and Heart Health</b>\nLow folate levels are associated with decreased brain function and an increased risk of dementia. Folic acid supplements may improve brain function and alleviate symptoms of depression.\nFolic acid contributes to improved heart health by reducing high blood pressure and the overall risk of heart disease and stroke.\n\n<b>Staying Healthy After Menopause</b>\nFolic acid continues to be beneficial after menopause, potentially reducing the risk of certain cancers, type 2 diabetes, and rheumatoid arthritis.\n\n<b>Ensuring Adequate Folate Intake</b>\nNon-pregnant women of any age are recommended to consume 400 micrograms (mcg) of folic acid daily, while pregnant women may require 400-800 mcg.\nFolic acid is water-soluble and needs to be consumed daily as it cannot be stored in the body.\n
    </string>
    <string name="fh3"><b>✤ Folic Acid-Rich Foods</b>
    </string>
    <string name="f3">Incorporating folic acid and folate-rich foods into your diet can bolster your folic acid intake. Some examples include:\n
    • Beans and legumes\n
    • Citrus juices\n
    • Egg yolks\n
    • Enriched breads, cereals, and other grain products\n
    • Fruits\n
    • Leafy green vegetables\n
    • Nuts and seeds\n\n<b>Folic Acid Supplements</b>\nMany women opt to supplement their folic acid intake to ensure they meet their daily requirements. It \'s crucial to consult a healthcare professional to determine the appropriate dosage, especially during pregnancy. Excessive folic acid intake can mask a deficiency in vitamin B12, leading to nerve damage.\n
    </string>
    <string name="fh4"><b>✤ Conclusion</b>
    </string>
    <string name="f4">Folic acid is an essential nutrient for women, offering a multitude of health benefits. Whether through diet or supplements, maintaining an adequate intake of folic acid is crucial for optimal health. Consult with a healthcare provider to determine the best approach for your specific needs and enjoy the lifelong benefits of folic acid.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="fs1">Benefits, Side Effects, Dosage, and Interactions\nWebsite: https://www.verywellhealth.com/folic-acid-benefits-715983</string>
    <string name="fs2">Folic Acid: Benefits, Foods, Deficiency, and More\nWebsite: https://www.healthline.com/nutrition/folic-acid</string>
    <string name="fs3">Folate | Linus Pauling Institute | Oregon State University\nWebsite: https://lpi.oregonstate.edu/mic/vitamins/folate</string>
    <string name="fs4">Vitamin B12 or folate deficiency anaemia - NHS\nWebsite: https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Folate-HealthProfessional</string>
    <string name="fs5">Folate (folic acid) - Mayo Clinic\nWebsite: https://www.mayoclinic.org/drugs-supplements-folate/art-20364625</string>
    <string name="fs6">Effect of folic acid and vitamin B12 on DNA methylation - WCRF International\nWebsite: https://www.wcrf.org/researchwefund/effect-of-folic-acid-and-vitamin-b12-supplementation-on-dna-methylation/</string>
    <string name="fs7">The Role of Micronutrients in DNA Synthesis and Maintenance\nWebsite: https://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/978–1–4757–3230–6_10</string>
    <string name="fs8">Folic Acid Supplementation for Prevention of Neural Tube Defects\nWebsite: https://www.cdc.gov/ncbddd/folicacid/index.html</string>
    <string name="fs9">How to Increase Red Blood Cells: Foods, Lifestyle, and More\nWebsite: https://www.verywellhealth.com/how-to-increase-red-blood-cells-5211734</string>
    <string name="fs10">Red Blood Cell Production - Hematology and Oncology - Merck Manuals\nWebsite: https://www.merckmanuals.com/professional/hematology-and-oncology/approach-to-the-patient-with-anemia/red-blood-cell-production</string>
    <string name="fs11">Folic Acid Deficiency Anemia\nWebsite: https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/folate-deficiency-anemia</string>
    <string name="fs12">Folate (Folic Acid) – Vitamin B9 | The Nutrition Source | Harvard T.H\nWebsite: https://www.hsph.harvard.edu/nutritionsource/folic-acid/</string>
    <string name="rfs13">Folate deficiency: MedlinePlus Medical Encyclopedia\nWebsite: https://medlineplus.gov/ency/article/000354.htm</string>
    <string name="fs14">Your Brain on Folate | Psychology Today\nWebsite: https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/evolutionary-psychiatry/201606/your-brain-folate</string>
    <string name="fs15">6 Effects of Folic Acid on the Brain | ImproveMemory.org\nWebsite: https://www.improvememory.org/blog/how-to-improve-memory/vitamins-minerals-supplements/6-effects-of-folic-acid-on-the-brain/</string>
    <string name="fs16">Role of Folate in Healthy Human Brain Function - Life Extension\nWebsite: https://www.lifeextension.com/magazine/2017/9/folate-improves-brain-function</string>
    <string name="fs17">Folic Acid (B9) - How Does It Help With Menopause?\nWebsite: https://www.menopause.sg/glossary/b-9-folic-acid</string>
    <string name="fs18">Why every woman needs folic acid | UCLA Health\nWebsite: https://www.uclahealth.org/news/why-every-woman-needs-folic-acid</string>
    <string name="fs19">Folic acid, a B vitamin, lowers stroke risk in people … - Harvard Health\nWebsite: https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/folic-acid-a-b-vitamin-lowers-stroke-risk-in-people-with-high-blood-pressure-201503177810</string>
    <string name="fs20">Folate - Consumer - Office of Dietary Supplements (ODS)\nWebsite: https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Folate-Consumer/</string>

    <string name="desclaimerOfFolicAcid"><font size="16"><b>!Disclaimer:</b></font>\nThe information in "Nourishing Beginnings: Prenatal Nutrition Guide" is for general informational purposes. Sources include ACOG, health.gov, Johns Hopkins Medicine, the University of Michigan, and nutrition.gov. Consult healthcare professionals for personalized advice. The author, Rakibul Islam Mehedi, and sources don \'t endorse specific products. Verify the information and seek guidance from healthcare providers. External sources \' inclusion doesn \'t guarantee accuracy. The guide may not cover every aspect, and new research may have emerged. Consult healthcare providers for personalized advice on caloric intake, weight gain, foods to avoid, and supplements. Individual pregnancies vary; seek support from professionals and pregnancy groups. Always consult healthcare providers for personalized medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment.
        \n\nRegards.
    </string>
    <!--    END_OF_FOLIC_ACID-->

    <!--    START_OF_ALCOHOL-->
    <string name="alcoHeading">Navigating the Crucial Choices: Alcohol, Smoking, and Cannabis Use During Pregnancy</string>
    <string name="alH1"><b>✤ Alcohol Consumption During Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="al1">Prenatal alcohol consumption is a significant cause of birth defects worldwide, leading to fetal alcohol spectrum disorder (FASD), which encompasses the mental and physical effects of alcohol exposure during pregnancy. FASD is a permanent disability.</string>
    <string name="al1.1">\n<b>Important Facts</b>\n• Alcohol is teratogenic, posing harm to the developing baby.\n• Consuming alcohol at any point during pregnancy can be perilous as the baby \'s brain and central nervous system are undergoing crucial development during this period.\n• If you have used alcohol and discover you are pregnant, consult your doctor for guidance. It \'s never too late to stop drinking.\n• If you struggle to abstain from alcohol during pregnancy, seek support from relevant sources like hospitals, community services, or family members. It \'s advisable to minimize alcohol consumption as much as possible.\n
    </string>
    <string name="al1.2"><b>Common Questions\n</b><b>How much drinking causes FASD?</b>\nDespite extensive research, there is no known safe level of alcohol consumption during pregnancy.\n\n<b>Do children grow out of FASD?</b>\nFASD is a permanent disability. However, supportive strategies and interventions such as educational services, speech therapy, and suitable environments can enhance outcomes, behaviors, and health.\n\n<b>If my baby is exposed to alcohol, will they have FASD?</b>\nThe impact of alcohol on a child \'s development varies depending not only on the amount and frequency of alcohol consumption but also on other factors such as genetics, diet, age, and trauma. Some children are more vulnerable than others.\n\n<b>Will my partner \'s drinking cause FASD?</b>\nFASD is caused by alcohol passing to the baby through the umbilical cord during pregnancy. However, a partner \'s drinking may influence your own. Seeking your partner \'s support in quitting drinking is beneficial.\n
    </string>
    <string name="alH2"><b>✤ Smoking and Vaping During Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="al2">Smoking cigarettes or vaping during pregnancy can have detrimental effects on both the mother and the baby.\n\n<b>Important Facts</b>\n
    • Smoking during pregnancy heightens the risk of various problems such as low birth weight, stillbirth, miscarriage, fetal growth restriction, premature birth, premature placental dissection, and sudden infant death syndrome (SIDS).\n
    • Secondhand smoke is also hazardous during pregnancy.\n
    • E-cigarettes (Vape) can expose growing children to nicotine and other harmful substances.\n
    </string>
    <string name="al2.1"><b>Common Questions\n</b><b>I only smoke a few cigarettes a day. Should I still quit?</b>\nAll types of smoke are harmful to you and your baby. It \'s advised to quit smoking as soon as possible.\n\n<b>What about vaping while pregnant?\n</b>Although e-cigarettes contain fewer harmful chemicals than cigarettes, they still contain nicotine, which can adversely affect the baby. Consult your doctor for options to quit nicotine during pregnancy.\n\n<b>Is it okay for me to smoke after the baby is born?\n</b>You and your baby shouldn \'t smoke. Reintroducing smoking post-birth exposes your child to the dangers of secondhand smoke.\n\n<b>I want to quit. Where can I find help?\n</b>Seek support and advice from your healthcare provider to lead a smoke-free life.\n
    </string>
    <string name="alH3"><b>✤ Cannabis Use During Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="al3">The legalization of marijuana in some countries has raised concerns about its use during pregnancy.\n\n<b>Important Facts</b>\n• There is no known safe amount of cannabis use during pregnancy.\n• Using marijuana during pregnancy can expose the baby to the harmful compound THC, which can impact healthy growth and development.\n• Research suggests that marijuana use during pregnancy may lead to lower weight gain and affect the child \'s brain and physical development, as well as potentially causing behavior problems later in life.\n\n<b>Common Questions</b>\n<b>Can I use cannabis to treat morning sickness?</b>\nMarijuana is not recommended for treating morning sickness or other pregnancy-related symptoms. Discuss alternative solutions with your doctor.\n\n<b>Can I use medical cannabis during my pregnancy?\n</b>Medical marijuana has similar effects on the child as recreational marijuana. Consult your doctor if you use medical marijuana during pregnancy.\n\n<b>What about CBD products? Can I use them during my pregnancy?\n</b>The effects of CBD during pregnancy are not fully understood. As a precaution, it is safest not to use CBD products during pregnancy.\n\nOverall, it \'s crucial to prioritize the well-being of both the mother and the baby by avoiding alcohol, smoking, and cannabis use during pregnancy and seeking professional guidance when needed.\n
    </string>
    <string name="desclaimerAlcohol"><b>Disclaimer:</b>\nThe information in "Alcohol, Smoking, and Cannabis Use During Pregnancy" is for general informational purposes only. It does not substitute for professional medical advice. Consult healthcare professionals for personalized guidance. The author, Rakibul Islam Mehedi, and the sources mentioned do not endorse specific products. Verify information and seek advice from healthcare providers for accurate decisions regarding pregnancy choices. The content is subject to change based on evolving medical research. The author and sources are not responsible for consequences arising from the interpretation or application of the information. Always consult healthcare providers for personalized medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment.\n\n
    Regards.\n</string>
    <string name="AS1">Alcohol, smoking, and other substance use in the perinatal period: This is a practice pointer article from The BMJ that provides an overview of assessment and interventions for substance use in the perinatal period. It also includes some case scenarios and useful resources for healthcare providers and pregnant women.\n
web: https://www.bmj.com/content/369/bmj.m1627</string>
    <string name="AS2">Cannabis use during pregnancy and its relationship with fetal developmental outcomes and psychiatric disorders. A systematic review: This is a review article from Reproductive Health that analyzes factors associated with cannabis use in pregnant women and its perceived availability, risk perception, and the relationship between prenatal exposure to cannabis and developmental and mental disorders.\nWeb: https://reproductive–health–journal.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1176/s12978–020–0880–9</string>
    <string name="AS3">Substance use in pregnancy: This is a web page from the Government of Canada that provides information about substance use during pregnancy, including tobacco, alcohol, cannabis, and other drugs. It also offers some tips and links for quitting or reducing substance use.\nWeb: https://www.canada.ca/en/public-health/services/pregnancy/substance-use-pregnancy.html</string>
    <string name="AS4">Substance Use During Pregnancy: This is a web page from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) that provides information and statistics on substance use during pregnancy, including the effects of tobacco, alcohol, opioids, and other drugs on the mother and the baby. It also provides some resources and recommendations for prevention and treatment.\n
Web: https://www.cdc.gov/reproductivehealth/maternalinfanthealth/substance-abuse/substance-abuse-during-pregnancy.htm</string>
    <string name="AS5">Can marijuana use during and after pregnancy harm the baby?: This is a web page from the National Institute on Drug Abuse (NIDA) that provides research-based answers to common questions about marijuana use during and after pregnancy, such as the effects of THC on the baby’s development, the risks of using marijuana to treat morning sickness, and the impact of marijuana use on breastfeeding and parenting.
I hope these sources are helpful to you.\nWeb: https://nida.nih.gov/publications/research-reports/marijuana/can-marijuana-use-during-pregnancy-harm-baby</string>
    <!--    END_OF_ALCOHOL-->

    <!--    START_OF_ORAL_HEALTH-->
    <string name="oralHealthHeading">Smile Safely: The Ultimate Guide to Protecting Your Teeth and Gums During Pregnancy</string>
    <string name="oh">Welcome to the transformative journey of pregnancy, a time filled with joy, anticipation, and changes. Amidst the excitement of preparing for a new life, let \'s shine a spotlight on a crucial but often overlooked aspect: oral health. The link between a mother \'s well-being and the health of her teeth and gums during pregnancy is profound, impacting both her health and that of her baby.\n</string>
    <string name="oH1"><b>✤ Oral Health Changes During Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="oh1">Pregnancy is a miraculous journey marked by hormonal shifts that significantly influence oral health. Understanding these changes is crucial for expectant mothers to proactively manage their dental well-being.\n\n<b>1. Hormonal Influences on Gums and Teeth:\n</b>Pregnancy brings an increase in hormones, particularly estrogen and progesterone. Elevated hormone levels may lead to more sensitive gums and increased susceptibility to inflammation.\n<b>2. Increased Risk of Conditions Like Gingivitis:</b>The surge in hormones can elevate the risk of gingivitis, characterized by redness, swelling, and tenderness of the gums. Proper oral hygiene is crucial to prevent gingivitis from progressing.\n<b>3. Importance of Regular Dental Check-ups During Pregnancy:</b>\nRegular dental check-ups are critical to monitor changes and address emerging issues promptly. Communicate your pregnancy status to your dentist for appropriate precautions during dental procedures.\n\n</string>
    <string name="oH2"><b>✤ Common Dental Issues During Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="oh2">Pregnancy brings unique challenges to dental health. Understanding these challenges empowers expectant mothers to navigate them effectively.\n\n<b>1. Overview of Common Problems:</b>\nIncreased susceptibility to gingivitis is a primary concern. Recognizing early signs is essential to prevent more severe gum diseases.\n<b>2. Impact of Morning Sickness on Oral Health:</b>\nMorning sickness can contribute to dental issues due to stomach acids eroding enamel. After vomiting, mitigate the effects by rinsing your mouth with water or a fluoride mouthwash.\n<b>3. Changes in Taste and Cravings:\n</b>Dietary changes during pregnancy can influence oral health. Balancing cravings with a nutrient-rich diet is crucial for both maternal and dental health.\n</string>
    <string name="oH3"><b>✤ Maintaining Optimal Oral Hygiene</b></string>
    <string name="oh3">In the midst of pregnancy changes, maintaining optimal oral hygiene is key for the well-being of both the expectant mother and her baby.\n\n<b>1. Importance of Regular Brushing and Flossing:</b>\nBrush teeth at least twice a day with fluoride toothpaste. Make it a daily habit to use dental floss for cleaning between your teeth and along the gum line.\n<b>2. Choosing Pregnancy-Safe Oral Care Products:\n</b>Opt for fluoride toothpaste and alcohol-free mouthwash. Consult with your dentist for personalized recommendations.\n<b>3. Incorporating a Balanced Diet for Improved Oral Health:</b>\nInclude calcium, phosphorus, and vitamin D-rich foods in your diet. Stay hydrated to prevent dry mouth and support saliva production. By embracing these practices, expectant mothers can safeguard their smiles and lay the foundation for a healthy start for their little ones.\n</string>
    <string name="oH4"><b>✤ Nutrition Tips for a Healthy Pregnancy Smile</b></string>
    <string name="oh4">Maintaining a well-balanced diet during pregnancy nurtures overall health and plays a pivotal role in supporting optimal oral health.\n\n<b>1. Key Nutrients for Strong Teeth and Gums:\n</b><b>Calcium:</b> Found in dairy products, leafy greens, and fortified foods.\n<b>Vitamin D:</b> Obtained from fatty fish, fortified dairy, and sunlight exposure.\n<b>Phosphorus:</b> Present in meat, eggs, dairy, and nuts.\n\n<b>2. Foods to Include in the Diet for Optimal Oral Health:\n</b><b>Crunchy Fruits and Vegetables:</b> Apples, carrots, and celery act as natural toothbrushes.\n<b>Dairy Products:</b> Milk, yogurt, and cheese provide essential nutrients.\n<b>Leafy Greens:</b> Rich in vitamins and minerals, supporting overall oral health.\n\n<b>3. Hydration and Its Role in Preventing Oral Health Issues:\n</b>Adequate water intake prevents dry mouth and supports saliva production. Limit sugary and acidic beverages; water should be the primary choice. Incorporating these nutrition tips into your daily routine contributes not only to a healthy pregnancy smile but also to your baby \'s developing oral health.\n</string>
    <string name="oH5"><b>✤ Safe Dental Care and Procedures</b></string>
    <string name="oh5">Ensuring safe dental care during pregnancy is crucial for maintaining optimal oral health without compromising the well-being of the expectant mother and her baby.\n\n<b>1. Communicating Pregnancy Status to Dental Professionals:\n</b>Inform your dentist about your pregnancy for tailored care. Routine dental check-ups, cleanings, and preventive treatments are generally safe.\n<b>2. Choosing Safe Dental Treatments and Procedures:\n</b>Elective procedures may be postponed; X-rays are generally avoided, especially in the first trimester. Schedule routine dental check-ups during the second trimester when risks are lower.\n<b>3. Adopting Comfort Measures During Dental Procedures:\n</b>Bring a small pillow for back support during procedures. Use conscious sedation and anesthesia cautiously; assess necessity and safety on a case-by-case basis. By staying informed, communicating openly with dental professionals, and adopting a proactive approach to oral care, you can navigate dental procedures safely during pregnancy.\n
    </string>
    <string name="oH6"><b>✤ Managing Pregnancy-Related Dental Challenges</b></string>
    <string name="oh6">While pregnancy brings new beginnings, it can also present challenges to oral health. Proactive management of these challenges is essential for a healthy smile throughout this transformative journey.\n\n<b>1. Strategies for Minimizing the Risk of Cavities:\n</b>Limit sugary snacks and beverages. Maintain a diligent oral care routine; consider fluoride mouthwash under dentist guidance.\n<b>2. Coping with Oral Health Challenges Related to Cravings:\n</b>Choose healthier alternatives for sweet cravings. After eating acidic or sugary foods, make sure to rinse your mouth with water.\n<b>3. Balancing Hormonal Influences on Gums:\n</b>Practice thorough oral hygiene; consider gentle gum massage during brushing. If your dentist suggests it, incorporate antimicrobial mouthwash into your oral care routine.\n<b>4. Addressing Morning Sickness Effects on Teeth:\n</b>Rinse mouth after vomiting; delay toothbrushing for at least 30 minutes. Manage stress to impact oral health positively. Adopting these strategies allows expectant mothers to proactively manage dental challenges associated with pregnancy, ensuring a healthy smile throughout this remarkable journey.\n
    </string>
    <string name="oH7"><b>✤ Conclusion</b></string>
    <string name="oh7">As we conclude this holistic guide to oral health during pregnancy, remember that nurturing your smile is a celebration of your journey to motherhood. Embrace the changes, prioritize preventive care, nourish yourself with a balanced diet, and communicate openly with dental professionals. Your radiant smile is not just about dental care; it \'s a testament to your commitment to holistic health for both you and your family.\n\n<b>Wishing you a joyful and healthy pregnancy journey!</b>\n</string>

    <string name="disclaimerOralhealth"><b>Disclaimer:</b>\nThe content provided on this platform is intended for informational purposes only and should not be construed as professional advice. While we make efforts to ensure the accuracy and reliability of the information presented, users should not consider it a substitute for consulting with qualified professionals.\nUsers are strongly encouraged to seek guidance from relevant experts or professionals in specific fields to address their unique circumstances. Any reliance on the information within this content is at the user \'s discretion, and we disclaim any responsibility for any loss, injury, or damage resulting from its use.\nAlthough we strive to uphold the highest standards of accuracy and reliability, information may become outdated or subject to change. We do not guarantee the completeness, timeliness, or suitability of the content and recommend independently verifying all information before making decisions or taking actions based on it.\nThis disclaimer applies to all content generated through this platform. Users are advised to exercise discernment and seek professional advice tailored to their specific situations.
    </string>

    <string name="OS1"><b>Hormonal Influences on Gums and Teeth:</b>\nAmerican College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists: \nWeb: https://www.acog.org/clinical/clinical-guidance/committee-opinion/articles/2013/08/oral-health-care-during-pregnancy-and-through-the-lifespan</string>
    <string name="OS2">National Health Service (UK): \nWeb: https://www.plymouthhospitals.nhs.uk/display-pil/pil-progesterone-treatment-6525/</string>
    <string name="OS3"><b>Increased Risk of Conditions Like Gingivitis:</b>\nAmerican Dental Association: \nWeb: https://jada.ada.org/article/S0002–8177%2817%2930640–8/fulltext</string>
    <string name="OS4">Mayo Clinic: \nWeb: https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/gingivitis/symptoms-causes/syc-20354453</string>
    <string name="OS5"><b>Importance of Regular Dental Check-ups During Pregnancy:</b>\nAmerican College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists: \nWeb: https://www.acog.org/clinical/clinical-guidance/committee-opinion/articles/2013/08/oral-health-care-during-pregnancy-and-through-the-lifespan</string>
    <string name="OS6">American Dental Association: \nWeb: https://www.ada.org/en/resources/research/science-and-research-institute/oral-health-topics/pregnancy</string>
    <string name="OS7"><b>Common Dental Issues During Pregnancy:</b>\nAmerican Dental Association: \nWeb: https://jada.ada.org/article/S0002–8177%2817%2930640–8/fulltext</string>
    <string name="OS8">National Health Service (UK): \nWeb: https://www.leedsth.nhs.uk/assets/2de5681640/Oral-health-for-pregnancy-leaflet-Copy.pdf</string>
    <string name="OS9"><b>Impact of Morning Sickness on Oral Health:</b>\nAmerican College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists: \nWeb: https://www.acog.org/clinical/clinical-guidance/committee-opinion/articles/2013/08/oral-health-care-during-pregnancy-and-through-the-lifespan</string>
    <string name="OS10">Mayo Clinic: \nWeb: https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/morning-sickness/symptoms-causes/syc-20375254</string>
    <string name="OS11"><b>Changes in Taste and Cravings:</b>\nAmerican Academy of Family Physicians: \nWeb: https://www.aafp.org/pubs/afp/issues/2005/0401/p1321.html\nNational Eating Disorders Association: \nWeb: https://www.nationaleatingdisorders.org/</string>
    <string name="OS12"><b>Importance of Regular Brushing and Flossing:</b>\nAmerican Dental Association: \nWeb: https://www.ada.org/en/resources/research/science-and-research-institute/oral-health-topics/home-care \nCenters for Disease Control and Prevention: \nWeb: https://www.cdc.gov/oralhealth/basics/index.html</string>
    <string name="OS13"><b>Choosing Pregnancy-Safe Oral Care Products:</b>\nAmerican Dental Association: \nWeb: https://www.ada.org/en/resources/research/science-and-research-institute/oral-health-topics/home-care \nFood and Drug Administration: \nWeb: https://www.fda.gov/medical-devices/guidance-documents-medical-devices-and-radiation-emitting-products/oral-rinse-reduce-adhesion-dental-plaque-class-ii-special-controls-guidance-industry-and-fda-staff</string>
    <string name="OS14"><b>Incorporating a Balanced Diet for Improved Oral Health:</b>\nNational Institutes of Health: \nWeb: https://ods.od.nih.gov/ \nAcademy of Nutrition and Dietetics:\nWeb:  https://www.eatright.org/</string>
    <string name="OS15"><b>Nutrition Tips for a Healthy Pregnancy Smile:</b>\nNational Institutes of Health:\nWeb:  https://ods.od.nih.gov/ \nAcademy of Nutrition and Dietetics: \nWeb: https://www.eatright.org/</string>
    <string name="OS16"><b>Safe Dental Care and Procedures:</b>\nCommunicating Pregnancy Status to Dental Professionals:\nAmerican College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists: \nWeb: https://www.acog.org/clinical/clinical-guidance/committee-opinion/articles/2013/08/oral-health-care-during-pregnancy-and-through-the-lifespan \nAmerican Dental Association: \nWeb: https://www.ada.org/en/resources/research/science-and-research-institute/oral-health-topics/pregnancy</string>
    <!--    END_OF_ORAL_HEALTH-->

    <!--    START_OF_PHYSICAL_ACTIVITY-->
    <string name="physicalActivityHeading">Empowering Your Pregnancy Journey: The Benefits and Safety of Exercise"</string>
    <string name="p">Exercise is part of a healthy lifestyle and has many benefits in pregnancy.\n</string>
    <string name="pH1"><b>✤ Important facts</b></string>
    <string name="p1"><b>• For healthy pregnant women receiving prenatal care, exercise is safe and should be encouraged.</b>\n\n<b>Exercise can:</b>\n1. Help you sleep better.\n2. Improve your mood and energy level.\n3. Helps you prevent weight gain.\n4. Helps relieve constipation, back pain, and swelling.\n5. Help strengthen your work and delivery.\n\n<b>• Aim for 150 minutes of intense physical activity per week.</b>\nIf you are just starting, start with a light activity such as walking. Even 10 minutes a day can help. Gradually increase this time to at least 150 minutes per week and work out at least 3 days per week. Moderate exercise during pregnancy is safe for most people, but there are some situations where exercise is not recommended.\n<b>• Listen to your body.</b>\nSome people can work before early pregnancy. Others find that it is easy in the first few weeks of pregnancy, but normal activity can be resumed after morning sickness or extreme fatigue. Light to moderate exercise, such as walking, can improve your mood and increase your energy levels.\n<b>• It is important to fuel your body, stay hydrated, and avoid overheating.\n</b>Eat a small snack 15 to 30 minutes before exercise. Do not exercise on an empty stomach. Drink plenty of water before, during, and after physical activity to prevent heatstroke and dehydration. Also, avoid outdoor activities on very hot days.\n
    </string>
    <string name="pH2"><b>✤ Key message</b>\nBuild physical activity into your routine during pregnancy to help you stay healthy and feel your best.</string>
    <string name="pH3"><b>✤ Common questions</b></string>
    <string name="p3"><b>What are the best choices for exercise in pregnancy?\n</b>There are many aerobic and resistance activities you can do to get stronger. Many people find that they enjoy exercising in water, such as swimming or water aerobics. Choose activities that reduce the risk of falling or contact with others. Exercises you are already accustomed to (walking, swimming, low-intensity aerobics, cycling, or moderate-intensity training) are a good choice. A combination of yoga or gentle stretching may be effective.\n\n<b>What about pelvic floor exercises?\n</b>Pelvic floor exercises, such as Kegel exercises, help strengthen the pelvic floor muscles that support the uterus, bladder, and intestines. These muscles control urination and defecation and support the baby during pregnancy. Childbirth stretches and weakens muscles; This can cause problems controlling urine when coughing, laughing, or doing physical activity after birth. Pelvic floor exercises during pregnancy and after birth can help the bladder heal. Talk to your doctor about floor exercises.\n\n<b>I have never really been active. Should I start now that I am pregnant?\n</b>Exercise is an important part of health and can help you feel better during pregnancy. Exercise during pregnancy is safe and supportive as long as you do not have problems that prevent exercise. Slowly start listening to your body. Do not start a new exercise or more intense exercise without consulting your doctor.\n\n<b>Are there exercises I should not do?\n</b>To protect your child from injuries, avoid contact sports such as hockey, football, and basketball. Activities such as horseback riding or motorcycle riding, water skiing, diving, skydiving, or scuba diving can also be dangerous for your child. Don \'t exercise to the point where you feel tired or overdo it.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="disclaimerOfPhysicalhealth"><b>Disclaimer:</b>\nThe information provided in this article is for general guidance and informational purposes only. It is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the advice of your physician or another qualified healthcare provider regarding any medical condition or before starting any exercise regimen during pregnancy. The author and publisher do not accept any responsibility for any liabilities, losses, or damages arising from the use of this information. Pregnant individuals are encouraged to consult with their healthcare professionals for personalized recommendations based on their specific health conditions and circumstances.</string>
    <!--    END OF PHYSICAL ACTIVITY-->

    <!--    START OF MENTAL HEALTH-->
    <string name="headingOfMentalHealth">Mindful Motherhood: Strategies for Cultivating Positive Mental Health Throughout Pregnancy</string>
    <string name="m">Pregnancy is a unique and emotional journey for every individual. It \'s natural to experience a wide range of emotions, from happiness to worry and anxiety. Taking care of your mental health during this time is crucial as it is closely linked to your physical well-being. Understanding your emotions and seeking the necessary support is essential for a healthy pregnancy.\n</string>
    <string name="mh1"><b>✤ Importance of Mental Health Care</b></string>
    <string name="m1"><b>Physical Health and Mental Well-being</b>\n• Your body undergoes significant physical and emotional changes during pregnancy, making self-care vital for protecting your mental health.\n• Prioritizing nutritious eating and staying physically active can positively impact your mood and overall well-being.\n• Adequate relaxation is equally important for managing emotional health during pregnancy.\n\n<b>Open Communication and Support</b>\n• Expressing your thoughts and feelings honestly is encouraged. It \'s beneficial to confide in your partner, family, friends, healthcare provider, or trusted individuals.\n• Joining a pregnancy support group can provide valuable emotional support as fellow expectant mothers can relate to your experiences.\n\n<b>Understanding Depression During Pregnancy</b>\n• Approximately one in 10 individuals experience depression during pregnancy, which is influenced by hormonal fluctuations.\n• Recognizing the signs and symptoms of depression, such as persistent sadness, mood swings, and changes in appetite and sleep patterns, is crucial for seeking timely support.\n
    </string>
    <string name="mh2"><b>✤ Seeking Help and Support</b></string>
    <string name="m2"><b>Identifying and Addressing Depression</b>\nIf you suspect you may be experiencing depression, it \'s important to consult your healthcare provider for professional evaluation and support.\n\n<b>Antepartum and Postpartum Depression\n</b>Antepartum depression, occurring during pregnancy, and postpartum depression, experienced after childbirth, can significantly impact individuals and should not be left untreated.\n\n<b>Medication and Treatment\n</b>Consult your healthcare provider about the safety of continuing any prescribed medications during pregnancy, as certain drugs may pose risks to the unborn child.\n\n<b>Recovery and Normalcy</b>\nWith appropriate care and treatment, most individuals can overcome depression, including antepartum and postpartum depression, and eventually return to their normal selves. Seeking professional help is the initial crucial step towards recovery.\n\n</string>
    <string name="mh3"><b>✤ Addressing Common Concerns</b></string>
    <string name="m3"><b>Understanding Mood Swings</b>\nFluctuations in mood are common during pregnancy due to hormonal changes, and seeking emotional support is essential for managing these variations.\n\n
        <b>Antepartum and Postpartum Depression\n</b>Antenatal and postpartum depression are distinct conditions that can affect individuals during different stages of the pregnancy journey, necessitating understanding and support.\n\n
        <b>Medication and Recovery\n</b>Seeking guidance from healthcare providers regarding the safety and suitability of medications during pregnancy is crucial, and with proper care, recovery from depression is achievable.\n
    </string>
    <string name="mh4"><b>✤ Conclusion</b></string>
    <string name="m4">Prioritizing mental health during pregnancy is integral to overall well-being. Seeking support, understanding the signs of depression, and accessing professional care are vital steps in ensuring a healthy and positive pregnancy experience.\n</string>
    <string name="disclaimerOfMentalHealth"><b>Disclaimer:</b>\nThe information provided here is for general purposes only and should not be considered as professional or medical advice. Consult with a qualified healthcare provider for personalized guidance. Reliance on the content is at your own risk, and the author and platform disclaim any responsibility for consequences arising from its use. The views expressed are solely those of the author and may not represent official positions. Always seek professional advice for specific health concerns.\n\nRegards</string>
    <string name="mS1">The relationship between social support and mental health problems during pregnancy: a systematic review and meta–analysis, published in Reproductive Health journal in 2021. This article reviews the literature on the association between low social support and the risk of developing mental health problems during pregnancy.\nWeb: https://reproductive–health–journal.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1176/s12978–021–01209–5</string>
    <string name="ms2">The COVID-19 pandemic and mental health in pregnant women: A review article, published in Frontiers in Psychiatry journal in 2022. This article discusses the impact of the COVID-19 pandemic on the mental health of pregnant women and provides recommendations to improve mental health care during pregnancy.\nWeb: https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fpsyt.2022.949239/full</string>
    <string name="ms3">Depression During and After Pregnancy, published by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) in 2023. This article provides information on the prevalence, causes, signs, and treatment of depression during and after pregnancy.\nWeb: https://www.cdc.gov/reproductivehealth/features/maternal-depression/index.html</string>
    <!--    END OF MENTAL HEALTH-->

    <!--    START OF SEXUAL HEALTH-->
    <string name="headingOfSexualHealth">Understanding Pregnancy and Sex: What You Need to Know</string>
    <string name="s">Your baby is well protected by the amniotic fluid and the uterus. As long as you do not experience problems such as premature birth or placenta problems, intercourse will not harm your baby.\n</string>
    <string name="sh1"><b>✤ Important facts</b></string>
    <string name="s1">
    • During pregnancy, your sexual interests may transform. For some individuals, there might be an increase in cravings, while others may not experience the same due to factors like fatigue, bodily changes, or nausea.\n
    • If you have problems with your pregnancy (multiple births, high blood pressure, placenta previa), please talk to your doctor.\n
    • Most couples continue active sex during the first year of their child \'s life.\n
    </string>
    <string name="sh2"><b>✤ Key message</b></string>
    <string name="s2">If your pregnancy is healthy and everything going well, sex is safe for you and your baby.</string>
    <string name="sh3"><b>✤ Common questions</b></string>
    <string name="s3"><b>• Can having sex cause a miscarriage?</b>\nHaving sex during pregnancy does not cause miscarriage. Most miscarriages occur because the fetus is not growing normally.\n\n<b>• Should I still use protection while pregnant?\n</b>While pregnant, it \'s important to note that pregnancy doesn \'t protect against sexually transmitted infections (STIs). Contracting STIs can pose serious risks for both you and your baby. It \'s crucial to take necessary precautions and maintain sexual health during this time. If you are pregnant and having sex with a new partner or a partner who may have an STI, use a condom to reduce the risk.\n
    </string>
    <string name="s4"><b>If you have any concerns or questions, or if you experience pain or unusual symptoms during sexual intercourse, please consult your doctor.</b></string>
    <string name="disclaimerOfSexualHealth"><b>Disclaimer: </b>\nThe information provided here is for general informational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always consult with your healthcare provider for personalized guidance regarding your specific situation. The content is based on general knowledge and may not account for individual variations or specific medical conditions. The use of any information from this response is at your discretion and risk. We do not endorse or guarantee the accuracy, completeness, or suitability of the information provided.\n\nRegards</string>
    <!--    END OF SEXUAL HEALTH-->

    <!--    START OF IMMUNIZATION-->
    <string name="headingOfImmunization">Safeguarding Maternal and Infant Health: The Critical Role of Immunization During Pregnancy</string>
    <string name="i">Ensuring the health and safety of both mother and child is paramount, and one key aspect is the importance of immunization throughout the stages of pregnancy. Vaccines serve as a crucial defense against serious diseases, some of which pose life-threatening risks. Staying abreast of the latest vaccination recommendations and guidelines is essential for optimal protection.\n</string>
    <string name="ih1"><b>✤ Pre-Pregnancy Planning:</b></string>
    <string name="i1">Before conception, engaging in discussions with healthcare providers becomes pivotal. Ensuring that vaccinations, such as MMR and varicella, are up to date is crucial. These preemptive measures lay the foundation for a healthier pregnancy.\n</string>
    <string name="ih2"><b>✤ Tdap Vaccine:</b></string>
    <string name="i2">Incorporating the Tdap vaccine during each pregnancy is recommended. This vaccine guards against tetanus, diphtheria, and pertussis, offering essential defense for both mother and baby before the infant is eligible for vaccination. Regular updates from the CDC and ACOG ensure the latest information on Tdap vaccine during pregnancy.\n</string>
    <string name="ih3"><b>✤ Flu Vaccine:</b></string>
    <string name="i3">Recognizing the elevated risk of flu during pregnancy, obtaining a flu vaccine within the flu season (November-May) is advised. This not only safeguards the mother but extends protection to the infant, who remains vulnerable until six months of age. Up-to-date guidelines from the CDC and WHO govern flu vaccination during pregnancy.\n</string>
    <string name="ih4"><b>✤ COVID-19 Vaccination:</b></string>
    <string name="i4">Full dosage of the mRNA COVID-19 vaccine is recommended for pregnant individuals. Evidence suggests its safety and efficacy in preventing serious illness for both mother and baby. Continuous updates from the CDC, WHO, and other reputable health organizations guide decision-making regarding COVID-19 vaccination during pregnancy.\n</string>
    <string name="ih5"><b>✤ Family Protection:</b></string>
    <string name="i5">Educating family members on the significance of vaccines contributes to preventing disease spread, ensuring a secure environment for susceptible newborns. Resources from organizations like the CDC and WHO assist in conveying the importance of vaccines to family members.\n</string>
    <string name="iKeyMessage"><b>Key Message\n</b>Sustaining up-to-date vaccinations is critical to providing optimal protection against infectious diseases for both the mother and the baby.</string>
    <string name="ih6"><b>✤ Common Questions</b></string>
    <string name="i6"><b>• Safety During Pregnancy:</b>\nMost vaccines are deemed safe during pregnancy, with preference for inactivated vaccines. The CDC and ACOG continually update information on vaccine safety during pregnancy.\n\n<b>• Vaccinations While Breastfeeding:\n</b>Routine vaccines are generally safe during breastfeeding for both mother and baby. Guidelines from the CDC and the American Academy of Pediatrics provide updated information on vaccines for breastfeeding mothers.\n\n<b>• Children \'s Vaccination Schedule:\n</b>The meticulously designed vaccination schedule for children offers optimal protection during vulnerability. Parents are encouraged to consult pediatricians or healthcare providers for inquiries about their children \'s vaccination schedule. Credible sources like the CDC and the American Academy of Pediatrics provide updated information on children \'s vaccination schedules.\n
    </string>
    <string name="ih7"><b>✤ Conclusion:</b></string>
    <string name="i7">Remaining informed about the latest vaccination recommendations and guidelines empowers expectant mothers to make well-informed decisions, protecting themselves and their infants from serious diseases. Consulting healthcare providers and relying on credible resources ensures a comprehensive understanding of immunization during pregnancy.</string>
    <string name="disclaimerOfImmunization"><b>Disclaimer:</b>\nThis article provides general information about immunization during pregnancy and is not a substitute for professional medical advice. Individual circumstances may vary, and readers are advised to consult healthcare professionals for personalized guidance. The author and publisher do not guarantee the accuracy or completeness of the information, and any reliance on it is at your own risk. This content does not replace medical consultation, diagnosis, or treatment. The author and publisher disclaim any responsibility for adverse effects resulting from the use of this information. Always seek the advice of qualified health professionals for specific health concerns.\n\nReagards.</string>
    <string name="iS1"><b>Pre-Pregnancy Planning:\n</b>Before conceiving, discuss vaccinations with your healthcare provider. Recommended vaccines include MMR (measles, mumps, rubella) and varicella (chickenpox).\nCDC - Vaccinations Before Pregnancy: https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/pregnancy/vacc-before.html
    </string>
    <string name="iS2"><b>Tdap Vaccine:\n</b>It is advisable to receive the Tdap vaccine during each pregnancy. This vaccine protects against tetanus, diphtheria, and pertussis (whooping cough).\nAmerican Academy of Family Physicians - Tdap During Pregnancy: https://www.aafp.org/family-physician/patient-care/prevention-wellness/immunizations-vaccines/disease-pop-immunization/pertussis-vaccine-receiving-tdap-during-pregnancy.html
    </string>
    <string name="iS3"><b>Flu Vaccine:\n</b>Due to increased flu risk during pregnancy, getting a flu vaccine between November and May is advised. It protects both the mother and the baby, who cannot be vaccinated until six months of age.\nCDC - Flu Vaccination During Pregnancy: https://www.cdc.gov/flu/highrisk/qa_vacpregnant.htm
    </string>
    <string name="iS4"><b>COVID-19 Vaccination:\n</b>For pregnant individuals, receiving the full dose of the mRNA COVID-19 vaccine is recommended. Evidence suggests safety and prevention of serious illness for both mother and baby.\nUChicago Medicine - mRNA COVID-19 Vaccine in Pregnancy: https://www.uchicagomedicine.org/forefront/coronavirus-disease-covid-19/mrna-covid-19-vaccine-pregnancy-breastfeeding
    </string>
    <string name="iS5"><b>Family Protection:\n</b>Educating family members about the importance of vaccines can contribute to preventing disease spread. Ensure a safer environment for newborns, who are highly susceptible to infections.\nVaccinate Your Family: https://vaccinateyourfamily.org/
    </string>
    <string name="iS6"><b>Safety During Pregnancy:\n</b>Most vaccines are safe during pregnancy. Inactivated vaccines are generally recommended, while live vaccines are avoided unless there is a high infection risk.\nCDC - Vaccine Safety During Pregnancy: https://www.cdc.gov/vaccinesafety/concerns/vaccines-during-pregnancy.html\nCanada Health - Vaccination in Pregnancy Fact Sheet: https://www.canada.ca/en/public-health/services/publications/vaccines-immunization/vaccination-pregnancy-fact-sheet.html</string>
    <string name="iS7"><b>Vaccinations While Breastfeeding:\n</b>Routine vaccines are generally safe for both the mother and the baby during breastfeeding.\nCDC - Breastfeeding and Vaccinations: https://www.cdc.gov/breastfeeding/breastfeeding-special-circumstances/vaccinations-medications-drugs/vaccinations.html\nNHS - Using Vaccines During Breastfeeding: https://www.sps.nhs.uk/articles/using-vaccines-during-breastfeeding/</string>
    <string name="is8"><b>Children’s Vaccination Schedule:\n</b>Follow the carefully designed vaccination schedule for children to offer the best protection when they are most vulnerable.\nCanada Health - When to Vaccinate: https://www.canada.ca/en/public-health/services/vaccination-children/when-to-vaccinate.html\nCDC - Child and Adolescent Immunization Schedule: https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/schedules/hcp/imz/child-adolescent.html</string>

    <!--    END OF IMMUNIZATION-->
    <!--    START OF BREASTFEEDING-->
    <string name="headingOfBreastFeeding">Breastfeeding While Pregnant - Safety, Challenges, and Joys</string>
    <string name="b"><b>Introduction:</b>\nThe art of breastfeeding is a beautiful dance of nourishment and connection between a mother and her child. But what about continuing this journey while expecting another bundle of joy? In this comprehensive guide, we delve into the safety considerations, potential challenges, and the myriad benefits of breastfeeding while pregnant. Let \'s explore the tips for managing this dual role and what to anticipate when the new baby makes their debut.</string>
    <string name="bh1"><b>✤ Is It Safe to Breastfeed While Pregnant?</b></string>
    <string name="b1">For many moms who are thinking about nursing while pregnant, safety is a major worry. The good news is that it \'s generally thought to be safe to carry a healthy pregnancy. There is no evidence to suggest that nursing will deprive the fetus of nutrition. Generally speaking, breastfeeding does not induce early labor due to the release of oxytocin. If your pregnancy is high-risk, involves multiples, or you \'ve been told to avoid a particular activity, speak with your healthcare professional.\n</string>
    <string name="bh2"><b>✤ Challenges of Breastfeeding While Pregnant</b></string>
    <string name="b2">There are difficulties associated with this dual position. Breastfeeding can be unpleasant due to tender nipples and hormonal changes around the fourth or fifth month. However, discomfort can be reduced with careful placement and the use of breathing techniques. During this period, keep an eye on your breastfeeding baby \'s nutrition and be aware of any changes in milk production. It \'s critical to fight weariness, so make rest a priority, get assistance, and lead a healthy lifestyle.\n</string>
    <string name="bh3"><b>✤ Benefits of Breastfeeding While Pregnant</b></string>
    <string name="b3">The benefits extend beyond the physical act. Breastfeeding while pregnant fosters continued bonding and emotional connection with the older child. For the mother, it regulates hormones, offers emotional support, and stimulates uterine contractions beneficial for a healthy pregnancy.\n</string>
    <string name="bh4"><b>✤ Tips for Managing Breastfeeding While Pregnant</b></string>
    <string name="b4">Managing this dual role requires careful attention:\n\n<b>1. Nipple Care:</b> Experiment with positions and techniques. Warm compresses and nipple creams can provide relief.\n<b>2. Self-Care:</b> Prioritize rest, seek help, and maintain a balanced diet for both your pregnancy and breastfeeding.\n<b>3. Hydration and Nutrition:</b> Ensure ample water intake and a nutrient-rich diet for you and your babies.\n<b>4. Seek Support:</b> Join support groups and consult lactation consultants for guidance tailored to your situation.\n<b>5. Communicate with Healthcare Provider:</b> Keep your healthcare provider in the loop, discussing any concerns for personalized guidance.\n</string>
    <string name="bh5"><b>✤ What to Expect When the New Baby Arrives</b></string>
    <string name="b5">The journey continues after the new baby arrives:\n\n<b>• Tandem Feeding:</b> Breastfeed both children in the same sitting, prioritizing the newborn for essential nutrients.\n<b>• Changes in Breast Milk:</b> Anticipate changes in taste and composition, supporting your children \'s transition to a new breastfeeding dynamic.\n<b>• Weaning:</b> Gradual weaning is a personal choice; set boundaries and offer alternative comfort measures.\n<b>• Emotional Support:</b> The older child may need reassurance; provide emotional support and one-on-one time.\n
    </string>
    <string name="bh6"><b>✤ Conclusion</b></string>
    <string name="b6">Breastfeeding while pregnant is a unique decision, blending considerations of health, your child \'s needs, and professional advice. Challenges like nipple tenderness and changes in milk supply can be managed with self-care and support. Embrace tandem nursing for a special sibling bonding experience. Remember, your breastfeeding journey is uniquely yours—prioritize well-being, seek support, and relish the joys of this transformative time. Trust your instincts and savor the beauty of breastfeeding while pregnant.</string>

    <string name="disclaimerOfBreastfeeding">Disclaimer: The information in this article, "Navigating the Journey: Breastfeeding While Pregnant," is for general informational purposes. It does not replace professional medical advice. Consult your healthcare provider for personalized guidance. The authors do not guarantee the accuracy or suitability of the content. Use the information at your own risk. Individual circumstances may vary, so seek medical advice tailored to your situation. The authors are not liable for any loss or damage resulting from the use of this information. Verify the accuracy with a healthcare professional before making decisions.\n\nRegards.</string>
    <string name="BS1"><b>Identifies barriers faced by mothers and necessary supports for informed breastfeeding choices.\n</b>BMC Public Health Article: https://bmcpublichealth.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1176/s12889–021–12216–3</string>
    <string name="BS2"><b>CDC (Centers for Disease Control and Prevention):</b>\nNational Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (NHANES): Provides health and nutritional status data for US children and adults.\nRelevance: Useful for studying breastfeeding duration and exclusivity.\nPregnancy Risk Assessment Monitoring System (PRAMS): Collects information on maternal attitudes and experiences related to pregnancy and breastfeeding.\nNHANES Data: https://www.cdc.gov/breastfeeding/data/index.htm\nPRAMS Information: https://www.cdc.gov/breastfeeding/data/index.htm</string>
    <string name="BS3"><b>La Leche League International:\n</b>Resources: Provides information on tandem nursing while pregnant and breastfeeding during pregnancy.\nSupport and guidance for mothers navigating breastfeeding during pregnancy.\n La Leche League International: https://llli.org/breastfeeding-info/pregnancy/</string>
    <string name="BS4"><b>UNICEF DATA:\n</b>Offers notes on breastfeeding practices, including data on feeding infants exclusively with breast milk from birth to 6 months of age.\nGlobal Perspective: Insightful data on international breastfeeding practices.\nUNICEF DATA on Breastfeeding: https://data.unicef.org/topic/nutrition/breastfeeding/</string>
    <!--    START OF COMMON COMPLAINTS DURING PREGNANCY-->
    <string name="headingOfCommonComplaints">Navigating the Journey: Practical Tips for Managing Common Pregnancy Discomforts</string>
    <string name="cc">Pregnancy is a beautiful and transformative journey, but it can also bring about various discomforts and challenges. From morning sickness to hormonal changes, there are several common complaints that many pregnant individuals experience. In this comprehensive guide, we will explore these complaints and provide practical tips on how to effectively manage them.</string>
    <string name="ch1"><b>✤ Morning Sickness: Navigating Nausea and Vomiting During Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="c1">Morning sickness, characterized by feelings of nausea and sometimes vomiting, is a prevalent complaint during pregnancy. While the exact cause of morning sickness is not fully understood, hormonal changes and increased levels of human chorionic gonadotropin (hCG) are believed to play a role.\n\nTo alleviate morning sickness, try the following strategies:\n<b>• Eat small, frequent meals:</b> Going too long without eating can worsen nausea, so opt for smaller, more frequent meals throughout the day.\n<b>• Avoid greasy and high-fat foods: </b>These can be harder to digest and may exacerbate nausea.\n<b>• Consume dry starch foods:</b>Crackers, toast, or cereal eaten in the morning before getting out of bed can help alleviate nausea.\n<b>• Stay hydrated:</b>Drink plenty of fluids, such as water or ginger ale, to prevent dehydration.\n<b>• Try ginger products: </b>Ginger has been shown to reduce nausea, so consider using ginger drops, ginger ale, or ginger tea.\n<b>• Take prenatal vitamins as directed: </b>If prenatal vitamins cause stomach upset, consult your healthcare provider for alternative options.\n<b>• Avoid triggers: </b>Certain foods or smells may worsen nausea, so identify and avoid these triggers.\n
    </string>
    <string name="ch2"><b>✤ Dealing with Constipation During Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="c2">Constipation is a common complaint among pregnant individuals due to hormonal changes and the pressure that the growing uterus puts on the intestines. To manage constipation during pregnancy, consider the following tips:\n<b>• Increase fiber intake: </b>Eat foods high in fiber, such as fruits, vegetables, whole grains, nuts, and dried fruits.\n<b>• Stay hydrated:</b> Drinking plenty of fluids helps soften the stool and promote regular bowel movements.\n<b>• Engage in physical activity:</b> Regular exercise, even simple activities like walking, can help alleviate constipation.\n<b>• Consume prunes or figs:</b> These fruits contain natural laxatives that can aid in relieving constipation.\n<b>• Avoid laxatives:</b> Unless prescribed by your healthcare provider, avoid over-the-counter laxatives and opt for natural remedies first.\n
    </string>
    <string name="ch3"><b>✤ Coping with Fatigue and Low Energy Levels</b></string>
    <string name="c3">Fatigue is a common complaint during pregnancy, especially during the first trimester. Your body is working hard to support the growth and development of your baby, which can leave you feeling tired and low on energy. Here are some strategies to cope with fatigue:\n\n<b>• Get enough rest: </b>Prioritize sleep and rest whenever possible. Take short naps during the day if needed.\n<b>• Practice relaxation techniques: </b>Engage in activities like meditation, deep breathing exercises, or prenatal yoga to relax your body and mind.\n<b>• Maintain a healthy diet:</b> Consuming a well-balanced diet that includes nutrient-rich foods will help sustain your energy levels.\n<b>• Stay physically active:</b> Regular exercise can boost energy levels. Consult with your healthcare provider for suitable prenatal exercises.\n<b>• Ask for support:</b> Seek help from your partner, family, or friends to alleviate some of your responsibilities and give yourself time to rest.
    </string>
    <string name="ch4"><b>✤ Navigating Breast Tenderness and Changes</b></string>
    <string name="c4">Breast tenderness is a common discomfort experienced during pregnancy, particularly in the first trimester. It occurs due to hormonal changes and increased blood flow to the breasts. To manage breast tenderness, consider the following tips:\n\n<b>• Wear a supportive bra:</b> Invest in a well-fitting, supportive bra that can provide comfort and minimize breast movement.\n<b>• Apply warm or cold compresses:</b> Use a warm compress or ice pack on your breasts to alleviate discomfort.\n<b>• Opt for soft fabrics:</b> Choose clothing made from soft, breathable fabrics that won \'t irritate your sensitive breasts.\n<b>• Avoid harsh soaps or lotions:</b> Use mild, fragrance-free products to cleanse and moisturize your breasts.\n<b>• Maintain proper posture:</b> Good posture can help alleviate breast discomfort by reducing strain on the chest muscles.\n
    </string>
    <string name="ch5"><b>✤ Addressing Frequent Urination</b></string>
    <string name="c5">Frequent urination is a common complaint during pregnancy, particularly in the first and third trimesters. It occurs due to hormonal changes, increased blood flow to the kidneys, and the growing uterus putting pressure on the bladder. To manage frequent urination, consider the following tips:\n\n<b>• Empty your bladder:</b> Take your time when urinating to ensure that your bladder is fully emptied.\n<b>• Avoid consuming excessive fluids before bedtime:</b> Limit your fluid intake before going to bed to minimize nighttime bathroom trips.\n<b>• Practice Kegel exercises:</b> Strengthening your pelvic floor muscles through Kegel exercises can help control urinary urges.\n<b>• Wear comfortable clothing:</b> Choose loose-fitting clothing that won \'t put unnecessary pressure on your bladder.\n
    </string>
    <string name="ch6"><b>✤ Alleviating Leg Cramps</b></string>
    <string name="c6">Leg cramps, often experienced during the second and third trimesters, can be caused by factors such as hormonal changes, increased pressure on leg muscles, and changes in blood circulation. To alleviate leg cramps, consider the following strategies:\n\n<b>• Stretch your legs:</b> Perform gentle leg stretches before bedtime to help prevent cramps.\n<b>• Stay active:</b> Engaging in regular exercise, such as walking or prenatal yoga, can help improve blood circulation and reduce leg cramps.\n<b>• Stay hydrated:</b> Proper hydration can help prevent muscle cramps, so make sure you \'re drinking enough water throughout the day.\n<b>• Apply heat or cold:</b> Use a warm compress or cold pack on the affected area to relieve muscle tension and reduce cramping.\n
    </string>
    <string name="ch7"><b>✤ Managing Heartburn</b></string>
    <string name="c7">Heartburn, characterized by a burning sensation in the chest, is a common complaint during pregnancy. It occurs due to hormonal changes that relax the muscles of the digestive tract, allowing stomach acid to flow back into the esophagus. To manage heartburn, consider the following tips:\n\n<b>• Eat smaller, more frequent meals:</b> Consuming smaller portions can help prevent stomach distention and reduce the likelihood of acid reflux.\n<b>• Avoid trigger foods:</b> Spicy, greasy, or acidic foods can worsen heartburn, so identify and avoid your triggers.\n<b>• Stay upright after meals:</b> Avoid lying down immediately after eating to allow your body time to digest food properly.\n<b>• Sleep with your upper body elevated:</b> Use extra pillows or a wedge-shaped pillow to elevate your upper body while sleeping.\n<b>• Consult with your healthcare provider:</b> If heartburn persists or becomes severe, your healthcare provider may recommend safe antacids or other medications.\n
    </string>
    <string name="ch8"><b>✤ Managing Backaches</b></string>
    <string name="c8">Backaches are a common complaint during pregnancy, primarily due to the strain placed on the back muscles and ligaments by the growing uterus. To manage backaches, consider the following strategies:\n\n<b>• Practice good posture:</b> Maintain proper posture throughout the day, especially when sitting or standing for extended periods.\n<b>• Use proper body mechanics:</b> Lift heavy objects by bending your knees and using your legs instead of your back.\n<b>• Engage in gentle exercises:</b> Strengthening exercises, such as prenatal yoga or swimming, can help alleviate back pain.\n<b>• Apply heat or cold:</b> Use a heating pad or cold pack on the affected area to relieve muscle tension and reduce pain.\n<b>• Seek professional help:</b> Consult with a physical therapist who specializes in prenatal care for additional guidance and support.\n
    </string>
    <string name="ch9"><b>✤ Coping with Dizziness</b></string>
    <string name="c9">Dizziness can occur during pregnancy due to hormonal changes, low blood sugar levels, or a sudden change in position. To cope with dizziness, consider the following tips:\n\n<b>• Move slowly when changing positions:</b> Avoid sudden movements that can trigger dizziness. Take your time when getting up from a sitting or lying position.\n<b>• Stay hydrated:</b> Dehydration can contribute to dizziness, so make sure you \'re drinking enough water throughout the day.\n<b>• Eat regular meals and snacks:</b> Maintaining stable blood sugar levels can help prevent dizziness caused by low blood sugar.\n<b>• Avoid standing for long periods:</b> If possible, take breaks and sit down to prevent excessive strain on your body.\n
    </string>
    <string name="ch10">✤ <b>Addressing Swelling of the Hands and Feet</b></string>
    <string name="c10">Swelling, also known as edema, in the hands and feet is a common complaint during pregnancy. It occurs due to increased fluid retention and reduced circulation. To manage swelling, consider the following strategies:\n\n<b>• Elevate your legs:</b> Prop up your legs on a pillow or cushion to help reduce swelling in the feet and ankles.\n<b>• Wear comfortable shoes:</b> Opt for comfortable, supportive shoes that provide enough room for your feet to swell.\n<b>• Avoid standing or sitting for long periods:</b> Take breaks to stretch your legs and avoid prolonged periods of standing or sitting.\n<b>• Stay hydrated:</b> Proper hydration can help reduce water retention and alleviate swelling.\n
    </string>
    <string name="ch11"><b>✤ Coping with Pregnancy-Related Anxiety</b></string>
    <string name="c11">Anxiety disorders can occur before, during, and after pregnancy, causing feelings of fear, worry, and nervousness. To cope with pregnancy-related anxiety, consider the following strategies:\n\n<b>• Seek support:</b> Talk to your healthcare provider, partner, or a mental health professional to discuss your feelings and concerns.\n<b>• Practice relaxation techniques:</b> Engage in activities like deep breathing exercises, meditation, or prenatal yoga to calm your mind.\n<b>• Join support groups:</b> Connecting with other pregnant individuals who may be experiencing similar anxieties can provide a sense of community and support.\n<b>• Prioritize self-care:</b> Take time for yourself and engage in activities that help you relax and reduce anxiety.\n
    </string>
    <string name="ch12"><b>✤ Seeking Support for Depression During Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="c12">Depression can occur before, during, or after pregnancy, affecting your mood, energy levels, and overall well-being. It \'s essential to seek support and treatment for depression during pregnancy. Consider the following strategies:\n\n<b>• Talk to your healthcare provider:</b> Discuss your symptoms and feelings with your healthcare provider, who can provide appropriate resources and support.\n<b>• Seek therapy:</b> Individual therapy or support groups can be beneficial for managing depression during pregnancy.\n<b>• Engage in self-care activities:</b> Prioritize activities that bring you joy and help improve your mood, such as hobbies, exercise, or spending time with loved ones.\n<b>• Consider medication:</b> In some cases, medication may be necessary to manage depression during pregnancy. Consult with your healthcare provider to weigh the benefits and risks.\n
    </string>
    <string name="c13"><b>Remember, </b>every pregnancy is unique, and it \'s essential to consult with your healthcare provider for personalized advice and guidance. By understanding and effectively managing common pregnancy complaints, you can enhance your overall well-being and enjoy a healthier pregnancy journey.
    </string>
    <string name="cs1"><b>UCSF Health:\n</b>https://www.ucsfhealth.org/education/coping-with-common-discomforts-of-pregnancy</string>
    <string name="cs2"><b>UStanford Children \'s Health:\n</b>https://www.stanfordchildrens.org/en/topic/default?id=common-discomforts-during-pregnancy-85-P01207</string>
    <string name="cs3"><b>American Pregnancy Association:\n</b>https://americanpregnancy.org/healthy-pregnancy/pregnancy-concerns/7-common-discomforts-of-pregnancy/</string>
    <string name="cs4"><b>Tommy \'s:\n</b>https://americanpregnancy.org/healthy-pregnancy/pregnancy-concerns/7-common-discomforts-of-pregnancy/</string>
    <string name="cs5"><b>Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC):\n</b>https://www.tommys.org/pregnancy-information/im-pregnant/early-pregnancy/10-common-health-problems-in-pregnancy</string>
    <!--    END OF COMMON COMPLAINTS DURING PREGNANCY-->
    <!--     START OF FETAL DEVELOPMENT-->
    <string name="headingoffetalDevelopmet">The Phase of Fetal Development in the womb.\n<font size="14">nKnow more about how your baby is growing and developing</font></string>
    <!--    START OF Preparing For birth-->

    <string name="w1_1"><b>Weeks 1-2 (Menstrual Period):</b> \nThe menstrual cycle begins, and conception typically occurs around the end of week 2.</string>
    <string name="w1_2"><b>Week 3 (Embryo Development Starts):</b> \nFertilization leads to the formation of a zygote. Cell division begins, and the zygote travels down the fallopian tube.</string>
    <string name="w1_3"><b>Week 4 (Implantation):</b> \nThe blastocyst implants into the uterus lining. The inner cell mass differentiates into the embryonic disc, which will become the embryo.</string>
    <string name="w1_4"><b>Week 5 (Beginning Organ Formation):</b> \nBasic structures of the brain, spinal cord, and heart start forming. The embryo is about the size of a sesame seed.</string>
    <string name="w1_5"><b>Week 6 (Heartbeat):</b> \nThe fetal heartbeat often becomes detectable via ultrasound. Limb buds appear, and facial features start taking shape.</string>
    <string name="w1_6"><b>Week 7 (Organ Development):</b> \nOrgans such as the lungs, liver, and stomach begin development. Arm and leg buds become more defined.</string>
    <string name="w1_7"><b>Week 8 (Fetus Emerges):</b> \nThe embryo is now referred to as a fetus. It \'s about the size of a raspberry, and facial features continue to develop. Arm and leg joints become more articulated.</string>
    <string name="w1to8D">In the first eight weeks of pregnancy, the developing baby is an embryo, and its weight is not commonly measured during this period. Instead, gestational age is used as a reference. By the end of the eighth week, the embryo is approximately 1.6 to 2.5 centimeters (0.6 to 1 inch) long. Specific weight during this stage is challenging due to ongoing development and individual variations. The focus is generally on overall growth and formation of crucial structures. If you have pregnancy-related concerns, consulting with a healthcare professional for personalized advice is recommended.</string>
    <string name="w1to8Heading"><font size="20"><b>Weeks 1 to 8</b></font>\nKnow more about how your baby is growing and developing </string>

    <string name="w9to12">During weeks 9 to 12 of pregnancy, the developing baby undergoes significant changes and is referred to as a fetus. At this stage:</string>
    <string name="w9_1"><b>Size and Features:</b> \nThe fetus grows to approximately 7 to 10 centimeters (around 3 to 4 inches), with ongoing formation of facial features, limbs, and essential organs.</string>
    <string name="w9_2"><b>Organ and System Development:</b> \nVital organs like the heart, brain, kidneys, and liver are present and starting to function. The fetus begins spontaneous movements, though these might not be noticeable to the mother just yet.</string>
    <string name="w9_3"><b>Gender Development:</b> \nWhile genitals begin to take shape, determining the baby \'s gender through ultrasound remains challenging during this phase.</string>
    <string name="w9_4"><b>Placenta and Umbilical Cord:</b> \nThe placenta and umbilical cord mature, facilitating the exchange of nutrients and waste between the mother and fetus.</string>
    <string name="w9_5"><b>Fetal Heartbeat:</b> \nThe fetal heartbeat becomes detectable, typically around weeks 10 to 12.</string>
    <string name="w9to12D">It \'s crucial to note that these milestones are approximate, and individual pregnancies can differ. Regular prenatal check-ups and ultrasounds are key for monitoring the pregnancy \'s health and progression. If you have specific questions or concerns, consulting with a healthcare professional is recommended.</string>
    <string name="w9to12Heading"><font size="20"><b>Weeks 9 to 12</b></font>\nKnow more about how your baby is growing and developing</string>

    <string name="w13to16Heading"><font size="20"><b>Weeks 13 to 16</b></font>\nKnow more about how your baby is growing and developing</string>
    <string name="w13to16">Between weeks 13 and 16 of pregnancy, the fetus continues to grow and develop, reaching important milestones:</string>
    <string name="w13_1"><b>Size and Appearance:</b> \nBy the end of the 16th week, the fetus is usually around 10 to 15 centimeters (4 to 6 inches) long. Facial features become more defined, and the body takes on a more proportional appearance.</string>
    <string name="w13_2"><b>Organ Maturation:</b> \nOrgans such as the kidneys, liver, and intestines are maturing, and the fetus begins to practice swallowing amniotic fluid. The digestive system is gradually becoming functional.</string>
    <string name="w13_3"><b>Movement:</b> \nThe fetus \'s movements become more coordinated, and mothers may start feeling the first fluttering sensations known as "quickening."</string>
    <string name="w13_4"><b>Skeleton and Muscles:</b> \nThe skeleton is transforming from cartilage to bone, and muscles are developing, allowing for more purposeful movements.</string>
    <string name="w13_5"><b>Sexual Differentiation:</b> \nGender can often be identified during ultrasound examinations as the external genitals continue to differentiate.</string>
    <string name="w13_6"><b>Vernix Caseosa:</b> \nA protective coating called vernix caseosa begins to cover the fetus \'s skin, providing a waterproof barrier.</string>
    <string name="w13D">It \'s important to remember that these milestones are generalizations, and individual pregnancies may vary. Regular prenatal care and discussions with healthcare professionals are crucial for monitoring the well-being of both the mother and the developing fetus. If you have specific concerns or questions, consulting with a healthcare professional is advisable.</string>

    <string name="w17to20Heading"><font size="20"><b>Weeks 17 to 20</b></font>\nKnow more about how your baby is growing and developing</string>
    <string name="w17to20">Between weeks 17 and 20 of pregnancy, there are notable developments:</string>
    <string name="w17_1"><b>Size and Features:</b> \nBy the end of week 20, the fetus is around 15 to 25 centimeters (6 to 10 inches) long. Facial features become more distinct, and the body continues to grow.</string>
    <string name="w17_2"><b>Fetal Movements:\n</b> The mother usually starts feeling more pronounced movements, known as "quickening." These movements become more coordinated as the nervous system develops.</string>
    <string name="w17_3"><b>Organ Development:\n</b> Organs are maturing, and the fetus \'s circulatory and urinary systems are becoming more functional. The baby may start producing meconium, the first bowel movement.</string>
    <string name="w17_4"><b>Gender Reveal:\n</b> If not determined earlier, the baby \'s gender can often be identified through ultrasound during this period.</string>
    <string name="w17_5"><b>Vernix Caseosa and Lanugo:\n</b> The fetus is covered with vernix caseosa, a protective layer on the skin, and lanugo, fine hair that helps regulate body temperature.</string>
    <string name="w17_6"><b>Hearing Development:</b> \nThe fetus \'s ears are developing, and they may start responding to external sounds, including the mother \'s voice.</string>
    <string name="w17_7"><b>Bone Marrow and Blood Cells:\n</b> Bone marrow begins producing blood cells, supplementing the liver \'s role. The skeletal system continues to ossify.</string>
    <string name="w17D">As always, individual pregnancies may vary, and regular prenatal check-ups are crucial. If you have specific concerns or questions, it \'s advisable to consult with a healthcare professional for personalized guidance.</string>

    <string name="w21to24Heading"><font size="20"><b>Weeks 21 to 24</b></font>\nKnow more about how your baby is growing and developing</string>
    <string name="w21to24">Between weeks 21 and 24 of pregnancy, significant milestones occur:</string>
    <string name="w21_1"><b>Size and Viability:\n</b> The fetus grows to about 25 to 30 centimeters (10 to 12 inches) by week 24, and there is an increasing chance of viability if born prematurely, though specialized medical care would still be needed.</string>
    <string name="w21_2"><b>Weight Gain:\n</b> The fetus begins to gain more weight as fat deposits form under the skin. This contributes to a more proportional appearance.</string>
    <string name="w21_3"><b>Movement Patterns:\n</b> Fetal movements become more distinct and can be felt regularly by the mother. These movements may include kicks, rolls, and hiccups.</string>
    <string name="w21_4"><b>Lung Development:\n</b> While not fully mature, the fetus \'s lungs start producing surfactant, a substance that helps the air sacs inflate and prevents them from collapsing.</string>
    <string name="w21_5"><b>Brain Development:\n</b> The brain continues to develop rapidly, and the neural connections are becoming more complex.</string>
    <string name="w21_6"><b>Sensory Organs:\n</b> The fetus \'s sensory organs, such as the eyes and ears, continue to develop. The eyelids may start to open, and responses to light and sound stimuli can occur.</string>
    <string name="w21_7"><b>Survival Odds:\n</b> Advances in medical care mean that the chances of survival outside the womb increase during this period, though the baby would still require intensive care if born prematurely.</string>
    <string name="w21D">It \'s crucial to note that these are general trends, and individual pregnancies may differ. Regular prenatal care and communication with healthcare professionals are essential. If you have specific concerns or questions, consulting with a healthcare professional is recommended.</string>

    <string name="w25heading"><font size="20"><b>Weeks 25 to 28</b></font>\nKnow more about how your baby is growing and developing</string>
    <string name="w25to28">Between weeks 25 and 28 of pregnancy, several key developments unfold:</string>
    <string name="w25_1"><b>Size and Viability:\n</b> The fetus continues to grow, reaching a length of about 30 to 38 centimeters (12 to 15 inches) by week 28. Viability increases further, with a higher chance of survival if born prematurely.</string>
    <string name="w25_2"><b>Brain and Nervous System:\n</b> The brain undergoes significant growth and development during this period. The nervous system becomes more refined, and the fetus \'s ability to regulate basic bodily functions improves.</string>
    <string name="w25_3"><b>Lung Maturation:\n</b> While the lungs are not fully mature, the fetus continues producing surfactant, a substance crucial for breathing. Lung development progresses, enhancing the baby \'s respiratory capabilities.</string>
    <string name="w25_4"><b>Fetal Movement:\n</b> Movements become more coordinated, and patterns may emerge. The mother often feels a wide range of distinct movements, including kicks and stretches.</string>
    <string name="w25_5"><b>Eyelid Opening: </b>\nThe fetus \'s eyelids, which were closed earlier, may begin to open. The eyes are developing, and responses to light can occur.</string>
    <string name="w25_6"><b>Weight Gain:\n</b> The fetus starts to accumulate more body fat, contributing to a more rounded and proportionate appearance.</string>
    <string name="w25_7"><b>Kick Counts:\n</b> Healthcare providers may recommend kick counts to monitor fetal activity. Mothers are encouraged to track the number of kicks or movements within a specific time frame.</string>
    <string name="w25D">As always, individual pregnancies can vary, and regular prenatal care is essential. If you have specific concerns or questions, consulting with a healthcare professional is advisable.</string>

    <string name="w29heading"><font size="20"><b>Weeks 29 to 32</b></font>\nKnow more about how your baby is growing and developing</string>
    <string name="w29to32">Between weeks 29 and 32 of pregnancy, there are pivotal developments:</string>
    <string name="w29_1"><b>Size and Weight:\n</b> The fetus experiences substantial growth, reaching a length of about 38 to 43 centimeters (15 to 17 inches) by week 32. Weight gain becomes more pronounced, preparing the baby for a healthy birth weight.</string>
    <string name="w29_2"><b>Brain Maturation:\n</b> The fetal brain continues to mature, with increasing complexity in neural connections. This period is crucial for cognitive development.</string>
    <string name="w29_3"><b>Lung Preparation:\n</b> The lungs are nearly fully developed, with surfactant production continuing to enhance respiratory capabilities. The fetus practices breathing movements, a vital exercise for lung readiness.</string>
    <string name="w29_4"><b>Fetal Movement Patterns:\n</b> While the available space in the uterus decreases, fetal movements remain noticeable. The baby \'s kicks and stretches may become more deliberate.</string>
    <string name="w29_5"><b>Eye Sensitivity:\n</b> The fetus \'s eyes become more sensitive to light, and blinking reflexes are well-established. The baby can now perceive changes in light and darkness.</string>
    <string name="w29_6"><b>Body Fat Accumulation:</b> The accumulation of body fat increases, contributing to a smoother skin appearance and better temperature regulation.</string>
    <string name="w29_7"><b>Antibody Transfer:\n</b> The mother passes antibodies to the fetus, providing essential immune system support during the early weeks after birth.</string>
    <string name="w29D">These milestones are general indicators, and individual pregnancies may vary. Regular prenatal check-ups are crucial during this stage, and any specific concerns should be discussed with healthcare professionals.</string>

    <string name="w33heading"><font size="20"><b>Weeks 33 to 36</b></font>\nKnow more about how your baby is growing and developing</string>
    <string name="w33to36">Between weeks 33 and 36 of pregnancy, crucial developments continue:</string>
    <string name="w33_1"><b>Size and Positioning:\n</b> The fetus experiences further growth, reaching approximately 43 to 48 centimeters (17 to 19 inches) by week 36. The baby often shifts into a head-down position in preparation for delivery.</string>
    <string name="w33_2"><b>Weight Gain:\n</b> Substantial weight gain continues as the fetus accumulates fat layers, contributing to overall growth and preparing for a healthy birth weight.</string>
    <string name="w33_3"><b>Organ Maturation:\n</b> Organs such as the lungs and kidneys are nearly fully developed, and the digestive system is prepared for functioning outside the womb.</string>
    <string name="w33_4"><b>Fetal Movement Changes:\n</b> While space in the uterus is more limited, fetal movements remain, though they may feel different as the baby adjusts to reduced space.</string>
    <string name="w33_5"><b>Brain and Nervous System:\n</b> The brain undergoes final maturation stages, with continued development of neural connections and increased brain activity.</string>
    <string name="w33_6"><b>Amniotic Fluid Reduction:\n</b> Amniotic fluid levels may decrease as the baby takes up more space in the uterus. This reduction is a normal part of the late pregnancy phase.</string>
    <string name="w33_7"><b>Positioning for Birth:\n</b> The baby often settles into the pelvic region, engaging in the optimal position for birth.</string>
    <string name="w33D">It \'s essential to remember that individual pregnancies vary, and regular prenatal check-ups provide crucial insights into the well-being of both the mother and the developing fetus. Any specific concerns should be discussed with healthcare professionals.</string>

    <string name="w37heading"><font size="20"><b>Weeks 37 to 40</b></font>\nKnow more about how your baby is growing and developing</string>
    <string name="w37to40">In the final stretch of pregnancy, between weeks 37 and 40, key developments mark the countdown to birth:</string>
    <string name="w37_1"><b>Full-Term Status:\n</b> By week 37, the pregnancy is considered full-term, meaning the baby is mature and ready for delivery.</string>
    <string name="w37_2"><b>Size and Weight:\n</b> The baby continues to grow, reaching an average length of about 48 to 53 centimeters (19 to 21 inches) and accumulating additional weight. This growth contributes to a robust and healthy newborn.</string>
    <string name="w37_3"><b>Organ Maturation:\n</b> The last weeks focus on final maturation of the baby \'s organs, particularly the lungs and digestive system, ensuring readiness for life outside the womb.</string>
    <string name="w37_4"><b>Positioning for Birth:\n</b> The baby typically descends into the pelvic area, preparing for the birthing process. This descent, known as engagement, is a crucial step.</string>
    <string name="w37_5"><b>Amniotic Fluid Changes:\n</b> Amniotic fluid levels might decrease as the baby takes up more space, which is a normal part of late pregnancy.</string>
    <string name="w37_6"><b>Fetal Movement:\n</b> While space is limited, fetal movements persist, albeit in a more subdued manner due to the reduced room in the uterus.</string>
    <string name="w37_7"><b>Onset of Labor:\n</b> As the due date approaches, the mother may experience signs of labor, including contractions, changes in cervix dilation, and the release of the mucus plug.</string>
    <string name="w37D">It \'s important to note that individual pregnancies may differ, and labor can commence earlier or later than the expected due date. Regular communication with healthcare professionals and adherence to prenatal care recommendations are vital during this critical period. Any concerns or questions should be promptly discussed with a healthcare provider.</string>

    <!--    Partner Support During Pregnancy-->
    <string name="headingOfPartnerSupport">A Comprehensive Guide to Partner Support During Pregnancy</string>
    <string name="overV"><b>Overview</b></string>
    <string name="overViewText">Pregnancy is a transformative journey, and the role of a supportive partner is paramount in ensuring the well-being of both the expecting mother and the developing baby. From emotional support to active involvement in prenatal care, a partner \'s role is diverse and significant. In this comprehensive guide, we \'ll explore the various dimensions of partner support during pregnancy, highlighting their importance and the impact they can have on this extraordinary journey.</string>
    <string name="roleOfPartner"><b>Partner \'s Role During Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="role1H"><b>✤ Educate Yourself:</b></string>
    <string name="role1">Understanding the physiological and emotional changes during pregnancy is fundamental for effective support. A partner well-versed in these aspects becomes a cornerstone for informed decision-making and addressing concerns. The importance lies in becoming a knowledgeable ally and actively participating in the educational aspects of the pregnancy journey.\n\n<font size="17"><b>To do:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Read Together:</b> Dive into pregnancy literature as a couple, fostering joint learning.\n<b>• Attend Classes:</b> Enroll in prenatal classes to gain insights and share the learning experience.\n\n<font size="17"><b>How to:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Open Dialogue:</b> Encourage open conversations about what you \'ve learned, promoting shared understanding.\n<b>• Ask Questions:</b> Actively seek knowledge and engage with healthcare providers during appointments.
    </string>

    <string name="role2H"><b>✤ Emotional Support:</b></string>
    <string name="role2">Emotional well-being is the heartbeat of a healthy pregnancy. A partner providing emotional support becomes a pillar, alleviating stress and contributing to a positive environment. The importance lies in cultivating empathy, active listening, and reassurance throughout this emotionally charged period.\n\n<font size="17"><b>To do:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Be Present:</b> Actively engage in conversations, and be present during both highs and lows.\n<b>• Express Love:</b> Regularly express love, support, and excitement for the upcoming journey.\n\n<font size="17"><b>How to:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Practice Empathy:</b> Put yourself in your partner \'s shoes, understanding and validating their emotions.\n<b>• Create a Safe Space:</b> Foster an environment where your partner feels comfortable sharing their feelings.
    </string>

    <string name="role3H"><b>✤ Accompany to Appointments:</b></string>
    <string name="role3">Regular prenatal check-ups are not just medical visits but shared experiences that strengthen the bond between partners. Actively attending appointments ensures shared decision-making and a deeper understanding of the pregnancy progress.\n\n<font size="17"><b>To do:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Schedule Together:</b> Collaborate on appointment schedules to ensure joint attendance.\n<b>• Celebrate Milestones:</b> Treat each appointment as a milestone, acknowledging the progress.\n\n<font size="17"><b>How to:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Stay Informed:</b> Familiarize yourself with the healthcare plan and actively participate in discussions.\n<b>• Capture Moments:</b> Document appointments through notes or pictures to cherish the journey together.
    </string>
    <string name="role4H"><b>✤ Assist with Lifestyle Changes:</b></string>
    <string name="role4">A healthy lifestyle lays the foundation for a thriving pregnancy. Partners actively involved in adopting and maintaining healthy habits contribute to optimal development and reduce the risk of complications.\n\n<font size="17"><b>To do:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Cook Nutritious Meals Together:</b> Make meal planning a joint activity, focusing on nutrition.\n<b>• Exercise as a Team:</b> Engage in pregnancy-friendly exercises together.\n\n<font size="17"><b>How to:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Set Goals:</b> Establish health goals as a couple, encouraging each other along the way.\n<b>• Celebrate Achievements:</b> Acknowledge and celebrate lifestyle changes, reinforcing positive habits.
    </string>
    <string name="role5H"><b>✤ Prepare the Home:</b></string>
    <string name="role5">Creating a welcoming home environment is essential for the well-being of the growing family. Partners who actively contribute to setting up the nursery and childproofing establish a sense of readiness and anticipation.\n\n<font size="17"><b>To do:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Plan Together:</b> Collaborate on nursery design and set-up.\n<b>• Childproof as a Team:</b> Tackle childproofing tasks jointly.\n\n<font size="17"><b>How to:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Involve in Decisions:</b> Include your partner in decisions about baby furniture, decor, and safety measures.\n<b>• Create a Cozy Space:</b> Ensure the home environment is comfortable and conducive to relaxation.
    </string>
    <string name="role6H"><b>✤ Help with Physical Discomfort:</b></string>
    <string name="role6">Physical comfort is a key aspect of a positive pregnancy experience. Partners who actively engage in providing massages, assisting with physical discomfort, and making necessary adjustments contribute to a sense of care and connection.\n\n<font size="17"><b>To do:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Learn Massage Techniques:</b> Acquire basic massage skills for relaxation.\n<b>• Create a Restful Space:</b> Establish a comfortable and supportive environment.\n\n<font size="17"><b>How to:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Communicate Comfort Needs:</b> Encourage open communication about physical needs and preferences.\n<b>• Be Attentive:</b> Pay attention to cues indicating physical discomfort and proactively offer assistance.
    </string>
    <string name="role7H"><b>✤ Parenting Classes:</b></string>
    <string name="role7">Parenting classes equip partners with essential skills and knowledge for the journey ahead. Actively participating in these classes ensures both partners are prepared for the responsibilities of parenthood.\n\n
        <font size="17"><b>To do:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Enroll Together:</b> Jointly decide on and enroll in parenting classes.\n<b>• Practice Skills at Home:</b> Extend class learnings to practical situations at home.\n\n<font size="17"><b>How to:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Discuss Learnings:</b> Have regular discussions about class topics, reinforcing key takeaways.\n<b>• Support Each Other \'s Growth:</b> Recognize and celebrate each other \'s progress in learning new parenting skills.
    </string>
    <string name="role8H"><b>✤ Prepare for Labor and Delivery:</b></string>
    <string name="role8">Active participation in preparing for labor and delivery is crucial for a smooth and controlled birthing experience. Partners who engage in creating a birth plan and packing the hospital bag contribute to a sense of readiness.\n\n<font size="17"><b>To do:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Attend Birthing Classes:</b> Participate in classes that specifically focus on labor and delivery.\n<b>• Pack the Hospital Bag Together:</b> Collaborate on what essentials to include.\n\n<font size="17"><b>How to:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Address Fears Together:</b> Discuss any fears or concerns about labor, seeking guidance and support.\n<b>• Practice Relaxation Techniques:</b> Learn and practice relaxation techniques to implement during labor.
    </string>
    <string name="role9H"><b>✤ Embrace Emotional Changes:</b></string>
    <string name="role9">Acknowledging and supporting emotional changes is vital for mental health. Partners who exhibit patience and understanding during mood swings contribute to a nurturing environment, positively influencing the mother \'s emotional well-being.\n\n<font size="17"><b>To do:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Communicate Openly:</b> Encourage open communication about emotions and feelings.\n<b>• Create Stress-Free Zones:</b> Establish areas or activities that promote relaxation.\n\n<font size="17"><b>How to:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Be a Listening Ear:</b> Actively listen without judgment during moments of emotional expression.\n<b>• Participate in Relaxation Activities:</b> Engage in activities that reduce stress and promote emotional well-being.
    </string>
    <string name="role10H"><b>✤ Financial Planning:</b></string>
    <string name="role10">Financial stability is crucial for providing a secure future for the growing family. Partners who actively engage in budgeting, planning for parental leave, and discussing financial aspects contribute to a stress-free environment.\n\n<font size="17"><b>To do:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Create a Family Budget:</b> Collaborate on a budget that includes expected and unexpected expenses.\n<b>• Plan for Parental Leave:</b> Discuss and plan for financial implications during parental leave.\n\n<font size="17"><b>How to:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Regular Financial Check-Ins:</b> Schedule regular discussions to ensure financial plans are on track.\n<b>• Explore Support Resources:</b> Research and explore available financial support resources for growing families.
    </string>
    <string name="role11H"><b>✤ Be Available and Flexible:</b></string>
    <string name="role11">Being available and flexible demonstrates commitment and emotional support. Partners who adjust their schedules, prioritize each other \'s needs, and provide assistance whenever necessary contribute to a sense of security and connection.\n\n<font size="17"><b>To do:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Prioritize Communication:</b> Keep each other informed about schedules and availability.\n<b>• Be Adaptable:</b> Be willing to adapt plans based on the needs of the moment.\n\n<font size="17"><b>How to:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Schedule Quality Time:</b> Set aside dedicated time for each other amidst busy schedules.\n<b>• Anticipate Needs:</b> Anticipate and fulfill each other \'s needs, especially during moments that require support.
    </string>
    <string name="role12H"><b>✤ Celebrate Milestones:</b></string>
    <string name="role12">Celebrating milestones creates positive memories and strengthens the emotional connection between partners. Acknowledging and commemorating each step of the pregnancy journey contributes to a positive atmosphere.\n\n<font size="17"><b>To do:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Document Moments:</b> Capture moments through photos or journaling.\n<b>• Plan Celebrations:</b> Mark important milestones with small celebrations or gestures.\n\n<font size="17"><b>How to:</b></font>\n\n<b>• Reflect Together:</b> Take time to reflect on the journey, appreciating the growth and progress.\n<b>• Express Gratitude:</b> Express gratitude for each other \'s contributions and support throughout the pregnancy.
    </string>
    <string name="roleRemember">Remember, each pregnancy is unique, and ongoing communication and flexibility are essential. By actively participating and offering consistent support, you can strengthen your bond and navigate this exciting journey together.</string>

    <string name="adviceBtnText">More Bad habits to avoid…</string>
    <string name="tips"><u>Tips...</u></string>
    <string name="ps1">Quitting smoking, abstaining from alcohol, and adopting a healthier diet are crucial aspects of maintaining a healthy lifestyle, particularly during pregnancy. If you \'re an expectant parent, you may also consider making lifestyle adjustments to support your partner.</string>
    <string name="giveUpSmokingH"><b>✤ Give up smoking and Alcohol</b></string>
    <string name="giveUpSmokeP">Now is the perfect time to quit. Secondhand smoke can be harmful for your partner and your unborn baby.\nAnd, Eliminate alcohol consumption during your partner \'s pregnancy for the well-being of both.</string>

    <!--Urine Test-->
    <string name="urineH1"><b>Urine Test During Pregnancy</b></string>
    <string name="ur1H"><b>Is there a noticeable change in urine color during pregnancy?\n</b></string>
    <string name="ur1">Typically, urine appears as light yellow or transparent. However, this change is more pronounced in pregnant women, with their urine potentially transitioning from light yellow to dark yellow, even adopting an orange-yellow tint.\n\nThe variation in urine color is influenced by hydration levels. When the body is well-hydrated and urine is dilute, the concentration of urobilin decreases, resulting in a lighter shade. Conversely, dehydration elevates urobilin concentration, leading to a darker yellow color. Multiple factors contribute to the dynamic changes in urine color during pregnancy.\n</string>
    <string name="urH2"><b>Observing Changes in Urine Color during Pregnancy\n</b></string>
    <string name="ur2">A significant number of women utilize urine-based home pregnancy test kits to confirm their pregnancy status. Approximately two weeks after conception, these kits effectively identify the presence of human chorionic gonadotropin (HCG), a hormone released during pregnancy. The placenta, responsible for nourishing the fertilized egg embedded in the uterine walls, produces HCG.\n\nHCG levels exhibit a notable surge during the initial three months of pregnancy, gradually diminishing over the subsequent six months.\n</string>
    <string name="ur3H"><b>Precision of Urine Pregnancy Tests\n</b></string>
    <string name="ur3">Pregnancy tests available at drugstores boast an impressive 99 out of 100 accuracy rate, comparable to tests administered at a doctor \'s office. These tests operate by scrutinizing urine for the presence of human chorionic gonadotropin (HCG), a hormone exclusively produced in pregnant individuals.</string>
    <string name="discOfUrine">Disclaimer:\nThis urine testing guideline is for general information purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice. Consult with your healthcare provider for personalized guidance. The information may not cover all factors, and the creators do not endorse specific brands of pregnancy test kits. Reliance on this content is at the user \'s discretion, and the creators are not responsible for any consequences.</string>

    <string name="lentgh">Length: </string>
    <string name="height">Height: </string>
    <string name="weight">Weight: </string>
    <string name="compareText">Your baby is currently comparable in size to a</string>

    <string name="firstTrimesterDiet">Diet tips for First Trimester</string>
    <string name="seconfTrimesterDiet">Diet tips for Second trimester</string>
    <string name="thirdTrimesterDiet">Diet tips for Third Trimester</string>
    <string name="beautyTipsDuringPrgnancy">Beauty tips during Pregnancy</string>
    <string name="foodsAvoid">Foods to avoid</string>

    <string name="notes"><b>Note:</b>\nIf you are pregnant and have any health conditions such as Anemia, Thyroid issues, High Blood Pressure, Low Blood Pressure, or Diabetes, it is crucial to consult with healthcare professionals for a personalized diet plan.</string>
    <string name="firstTrimester"><font size="20"><b>Spinach: \n</b></font><b>• Nutrient Highlight: </b>High in folic acid.\n<b>• Importance: </b>Crucial for proper neural tube fusion in the first month after conception.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Lentils: \n</b></font><b>• Nutrient Highlight: </b>Rich in proteins.\n<b>• Importance: </b>Aids in the proper growth of baby \'s tissue and muscle throughout each trimester.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Lean Beef: \n</b></font><b>• Nutrient Highlight: </b>Excellent source of iron.\n<b>• Importance:</b> Essential for preventing iron deficiency; choose grass-fed, organic, and hormone-free options.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Salmon: \n</b></font><b>• Nutrient Highlight:</b> High in calcium and Vitamin D.\n<b>• Importance:</b> Supports bone health; one of the safer fish choices during pregnancy.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Collard Greens: \n</b></font><b>• Nutrient Highlight: </b>High in iron.\n<b>• Importance: </b>Addresses iron deficiency common in pregnant women.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Chicken: \n</b></font><b>• Nutrient Highlight:</b> High in iron.\n<b>• Importance: </b>Essential for creating red blood cells and ensuring proper oxygen supply to the body.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Broccoli: \n</b></font><b>• Nutrient Highlight:</b> Surprisingly high in iron.\n<b>• Importance:</b> Needed in the first trimester for the formation of red blood cells in the baby.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Eggs: \n</b></font><b>• Nutrient Highlight:</b> Excellent source of protein, calcium, and Vitamin D.\n<b>• Importance:</b> Essential for proper tone formation in the baby.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Asparagus: \n</b></font><b>• Nutrient Highlight:</b> High in Vitamin D.\n<b>• Importance:</b> Addresses Vitamin D deficiency, common in many pregnant women.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Nuts: \n</b></font><b>• Nutrient Highlight: </b>Extra source of protein.\n<b>• Importance: </b>Helps meet the increased protein needs during pregnancy.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Cottage Cheese: \n</b></font><b>• Nutrient Highlight: </b>Contains both calcium and protein.\n<b>• Importance: </b>Supports muscle and bone development in the baby.\n\n<i>Remember to incorporate a variety of these foods into your daily meals, maintain a balanced diet, and consult with your healthcare provider for personalized advice based on your specific needs during pregnancy.</i></string>
    <string name="secondTrimester"><font size="20"><b>Glass of Milk: \n</b></font>• Semi-skimmed milk is a rich source of calcium and magnesium.\n• Consider fortified soy products like soy yogurt as non-dairy substitutes.\n• Sufficient calcium during pregnancy supports the growth of the baby\'s bones and teeth.\n• Vitamin D supplementation enhances calcium absorption.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Baked Potato with Beans: \n</b></font>• Combining baked potatoes with baked beans creates a well-rounded dinner rich in fiber, magnesium, and iron.\n• Magnesium is essential for bone growth and the body\'s conversion of food into energy.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Variety of Vegetables: \n</b></font>• Include calcium and magnesium-rich vegetables such as broccoli, green beans, carrots, cabbage, and okra in your diet.\n• Use cooking techniques like stir-frying or steaming to preserve nutrients and prevent overcooking.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Sunflower and Pumpkin Seeds: \n</b></font>• A small handful of sunflower or pumpkin seeds, whether eaten as a snack or added to salads and yogurt, provides a significant boost in magnesium, iron, and omega-3.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Dried Fruit: \n</b></font>• Apricots, dates, and figs, rich in calcium and iron, make excellent snacks.\n• Enhance the nutritional content of low-fat yogurt by adding chopped dried fruit.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Brown Rice Vegetable Risotto: \n</b></font>• Pairing brown rice or wholegrain with mushrooms offers a wholesome combination of calcium, magnesium, fiber, and vitamin D.\n• Experiment with recipes like brown basmati rice with chicken and edamame bean pilaf or mushroom risotto with spinach.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Peanut Butter on Wholemeal Bread: \n</b></font>• Peanut butter, rich in iron and magnesium, is a good source of healthy fats.\n• Combine with fortified wholegrain bread for a filling snack.\n• Consider adding a glass of milk for an extra dose of calcium.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Cheese on Seeded Bread: \n</b></font>• Low-fat cream cheese on seeded bread provides a beneficial combination of calcium and magnesium.\n• Enjoy with a crisp salad featuring veggies like cucumber and radishes.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Hummus: \n</b></font>• Hummus is a tasty and low-fat source of iron and calcium.\n• Pair with a small wholegrain pitta or granary bread to add more magnesium.\n• Serve with crisp fresh veggies as a side.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Canned Sardines: \n</b></font>• Mash canned sardines, including the bones, on wholegrain toast or mix with spaghetti.\n• Opt for oil- or tomato-sauced sardines and consider adding a watercress salad for extra calcium and vitamin C.\n\n<font size="20"><b>A Little Dark Chocolate: \n</b></font>• Enjoy a small quantity of dark chocolate as a tasty way to increase iron and calcium intake, but do so in moderation.\n\n<i>Remember to incorporate a variety of these foods into your daily meals, maintain a balanced diet, and consult with your healthcare provider for personalized advice based on your specific needs during pregnancy.</i></string>
    <string name="thirdTrimester"><font size="20"><b>Snack Ideas: \n\n</b></font><b>Peanut Butter on Wholemeal Bread:\n</b><b>• Nutrients:</b> Iron, magnesium, and healthy fats.\n<b>• Details:</b> Create a satisfying snack by combining peanut butter with fortified wholegrain bread. Enhance it with a glass of milk for an extra calcium boost.\n\n<b>Cheese on Seeded Bread:\n</b><b>• Nutrients:</b> Calcium and magnesium.\n<b>• Details:</b> Spread your favorite cheese or low-fat cream cheese on seeded bread. Enjoy with a refreshing salad of crisp cucumber and radishes.\n\n<b>Hummus:\n</b><b>• Nutrients:</b> Iron and calcium.\n<b>• Details:</b> Keep low-fat hummus refrigerated. Serve it with crunchy raw veggies and either wholegrain pitta or granary bread for an additional magnesium kick.\n\n<b>Sardines in a Can:\n</b><b>• Nutrients:</b> Iron, calcium, magnesium, and vitamin C.\n<b>• Details:</b> Mash sardines on wholegrain toast, ensuring bones are broken up. Alternatively, mix with spaghetti, pine nuts, and parmesan for added nutrition. Choose between sardines in tomato sauce or oil. Serve with a watercress salad.\n\n<b>Dark Chocolate (In Moderation):\n</b><b>• Information:</b> Enjoy a modest serving of dark chocolate as a pleasant way to supplement iron and calcium. Consume sparingly.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Meal Ideas: \n\n</b></font><b>Fruits:\n</b><b>• Nutrients:</b> Fiber and vitamin C.\n<b>• Details:</b> Delight in fresh fruits like papaya, melon, strawberries, and kiwis. Cut them into convenient pieces for an easy on-the-go snack or pack some for later.\n\n<b>Tomato and Ham Salad:\n</b><b>• Nutrients:</b> Vitamin C and thiamine.\n<b>• Details:</b> Opt for lean ham for a thiamine boost. Mix with a vitamin-rich salad featuring lettuce, tomatoes, radishes, and sweet corn.\n\n<b>Bean Chilli:\n</b><b>• Nutrients:</b> Iron, fiber, vitamin C, thiamine.\n<b>• Details:</b> Prepare a spicy chili using canned kidney, black-eyed beans, borlotti, or cannellini beans. Enhance it with fresh peppers and tomatoes for an added vitamin C boost.\n\n<b>Lentils:\n</b><b>• Nutrients:</b> Fiber and thiamine.\n<b>• Details:</b> Add cooked lentils to dals, soups, stews, and salads for a tasty fiber and thiamine boost. Ensure soups have minimal salt.\n\n<b>Nuts and Seeds:\n</b><b>• Nutrients:</b> Thiamine and omega-3 fats.\n<b>• Details:</b> Incorporate thiamine-rich hazelnuts, walnuts, and sunflower seeds into cereal bars, breads, and breakfast cereals.\n\n<b>Baked Beans on Wholemeal Toast:\n</b><b>• Nutrients:</b> Fiber and thiamine.\n<b>• Details:</b> Enjoy thiamine-packed baked beans served with wholemeal or seeded bread. The fiber aids in maintaining consistent energy levels and combating constipation.\n\n<b>Avocado Salad:\n</b><b>• Nutrients:</b> Vitamin C, vitamin E, fiber, and vitamin K.\n<b>• Details:</b> Iron, fiber, vitamin C, thiamine.\n\n<b>Avocado Salad:\n</b><b>• Nutrients:</b> Vitamin C, vitamin E, fiber, and vitamin K.\n<b>• Details:</b> Toss avocados with walnuts, mango or orange segments, and vitamin K-rich watercress or rocket. Add a dressing for extra flavor.\n\n<b>Yeast Extract:\n</b><b>• Supplemental Nutrients:</b> Including thiamine.\n<b>• Details:</b> Spread thinly over bread and try it with tomatoes, cottage cheese, or mashed avocado\n\n<b>Brussels Sprouts:\n</b><b>• Nutrients:</b> Vitamin K and C.\n<b>• Details:</b> Add Brussels sprouts to stir-fries with spring onions, ginger, and garlic, or steam or microwave them as a side dish.\n\n<i>This diet provides a well-rounded and balanced approach to nutrition by offering a wide variety of nutrients and flavors. Don\'t forget to adjust it to your own nutritional needs and tastes.</i></string>
    <string name="foodsAvoidAticle">Paying attention to your diet throughout pregnancy is critical for the health and well-being of both the mother and the developing baby. Here\'s a list of foods to avoid while pregnant:\n\n<b>• High-Mercury Fish: </b>Avoid high-mercury fish since they can affect the growing neurological system of the fetus. Avoid mercury-rich fish like sharks, swordfish, king mackerel, and tilefish. Choose low-mercury options such as salmon, shrimp, and catfish.\n\n<b>• Raw Seafood: </b>Consuming raw or undercooked seafood may expose you to hazardous bacteria and parasites. Avoid sushi, sashimi, and raw oysters when pregnant.\n\n<b>• Raw Eggs: </b>Consuming raw or undercooked eggs may increase the risk of salmonella infection. Avoid eating homemade Caesar dressing, mayonnaise, and uncooked cookie dough.\n\n<b>• Unpasteurized Dairy: </b>Unpasteurized milk and dairy products may contain hazardous bacteria like Listeria. Choose pasteurized alternatives to limit the risk of infection.\n\n<b>• Soft Cheeses: </b>Soft cheeses such as Brie, feta, camembert, and blue cheese may have Listeria. Choose hard cheeses such as cheddar or Swiss, which are less likely to contain dangerous bacteria.\n\n<b>• Deli Meats and Hot Dogs: </b>Listeria contamination can occur in deli meats and hot dogs. If you decide to eat them, cook them sufficiently until steaming to lessen the risk.\n\n<b>• Caffeine: </b>Moderate caffeine intake is generally safe, but high consumption has been linked to an increased risk of miscarriage. Limit your caffeine intake to between 200 and 300 mg per day.\n\n<b>• Alcohol: </b>Alcohol can affect the growing fetus, causing birth abnormalities and developmental difficulties. It is suggested to avoid alcohol throughout pregnancy.\n\n<b>• High-Sugar and Processed Foods:</b> Consuming sugary and processed foods can lead to excessive weight gain and gestational diabetes. Choose a balanced diet that focuses on whole foods.\n\n<b>• Unwashed Produce: </b>Raw fruits and vegetables may contain hazardous microorganisms. Wash them properly before eating to reduce the risk of foodborne illness.\n\n<b>• Excessive Vitamin A: </b>Vitamin A pills and animal liver products can affect the growing fetus. Avoid taking excessive amounts of vitamin A pills.\n\<b>• Herbal Teas and Supplements: </b>Certain herbal teas and supplements may contain unsafe components during pregnancy. Before taking any herbal products, consult with a healthcare provider.\n\n<b><i>Pregnant women should meet with their healthcare professionals to develop a personalized and safe diet plan that takes into account their health problems and nutritional requirements during pregnancy.</i> </b></string>
    <string name="beautyTips">Beauty during pregnancy is essential for self-confidence, comfort, and emotional well-being. It promotes positive body image, enhances the connection with the baby, and contributes to maternal mental health. Engaging in beauty routines provides moments of relaxation, and empowerment, and prepares for postpartum well-being.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Skincare Routine: \n</b></font><b>• Moisturize: </b>Keep your skin well-hydrated with a gentle and pregnancy-safe moisturizer to prevent dryness and stretch marks.\n<b>• Sunscreen: </b>Use a broad-spectrum, pregnancy-safe sunscreen to protect your skin from harmful UV rays.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Hair Care: \n</b></font><b>• Gentle Shampooing: </b>Opt for mild, sulfate-free shampoos to keep your hair clean without stripping away natural oils.\n<b>• Avoid Chemical Treatments: </b>Steer clear of chemical hair treatments containing harsh ingredients like ammonia or formaldehyde.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Nail Care: \n</b></font><b>• Non-Toxic Nail Polish: </b>Choose pregnancy-safe, non-toxic nail polish if you want to paint your nails.\n<b>• Ventilation: </b>Ensure good ventilation if you choose to visit a salon for nail treatments.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Makeup Choices: \n</b></font><b>• Choose safe products: </b>Select makeup products free from harmful chemicals like phthalates, parabens, and retinoids.\n<b>• Avoid heavy makeup: </b>During pregnancy, consider lighter makeup to allow your skin to breathe.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Hydration and Nutrition: \n</b></font><b>• Stay Hydrated: </b>Drink plenty of water to maintain skin hydration and overall health.\n<b>• Balanced Diet: </b>Consume a well-balanced diet rich in vitamins and minerals for healthy skin.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Pamper Yourself: \n</b></font><b>• Facial Treatments: </b>Opt for gentle facials and avoid harsh chemical peels.\n<b>• Prenatal Massages: </b>Consider prenatal massages for relaxation and to alleviate any discomfort.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Sleep and Stress Management: \n</b></font><b>• Adequate Sleep: </b>Ensure you get enough sleep to promote skin regeneration and overall well-being.\n<b>• Stress Reduction: </b>Practice stress-reducing activities like meditation or gentle exercises.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Maternity Fashion: \n</b></font><b>• Comfortable Clothing: </b>Wear comfortable and breathable fabrics to accommodate your changing body.\n<b>• Supportive Bras: </b>Invest in supportive bras to provide comfort and prevent sagging.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Dental Care: \n</b></font><b>• Regular Check-ups: </b>Continue regular dental check-ups and cleanings for oral health.\n<b>• Safe Teeth Whitening: </b>Consult your dentist before opting for any teeth-whitening procedures.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Consult Professionals: \n</b></font><b>• Hair Stylist and Dermatologist: </b>If considering treatments, consult with a hairstylist or dermatologist experienced in pregnancy-safe options.\n<b>• Patch Tests: </b>Always perform patch tests before trying new beauty products to avoid potential allergic reactions.\n\n<font size="20"><b>Mindful of Fragrances: \n</b></font><b>• Choose Mild Scents: </b>Opt for mild and non-overpowering fragrances to avoid sensitivities.\n\n<i>Remember, individual experiences during pregnancy may vary, so it\'s crucial to consult with your healthcare provider before making significant changes to your beauty routine. They can provide personalized advice based on your health and specific circumstances.\n</i></string>
    <string name="noteBeauty"><b>Note:\n</b>Prioritize your well-being and consult with your healthcare provider before incorporating any beauty tips, especially if you are pregnant or have underlying health conditions. Every individual\'s situation is unique, and professional guidance ensures a beauty routine that aligns with your health and safety requirements.</string>

    <string name="testKitH1">Pregnancy Test Strips: A Comprehensive Guide to Understanding How They Work</string>
    <string name="testKitIntro">Pregnancy test strips, equipped with a convenient test window, have transformed at-home testing. Let\'s delve into their functionality!\n\n</string>
    <string name="testK1H"><b>Understanding pregnancy changes\n</b></string>
    <string name="testK1">Pregnancy initiates several changes in the body, including shifts in hormonal levels. Human chorionic gonadotropin (HCG), known as the \'hormone of pregnancy,\' increases during this period and is detectable in both blood and urine. Pregnancy test strips play a crucial role in identifying this hormone, specifically in urine.\n\nThe embryo actively secretes HCG upon attachment to the womb. Subsequent to embryo placement in the uterus, the HCG level rises rapidly. Pregnancy test strips provide a swift and efficient means to confirm pregnancy by monitoring the HCG hormone level in the urine. However, confirmation of pregnancy status can also be done by assessing the HCG level in your blood. Your doctor will take a blood sample, transmitting it to the laboratory for an HCG test. CMH Hospital Lahore, renowned for its well-established gynecology department, commonly performs the HCG pregnancy test. For more details, read about the HCG test in Pakistan.\n</string>
    <string name="testK2H"><b>Performing Pregnancy Tests Using Strips at Home: A Step-by-Step Guide\n</b></string>
    <string name="testK2">Performing a pregnancy test at home using strips is straightforward. Follow this step-by-step guide to ensure accurate and reliable results:\n\n<b>1. Obtain Pregnancy Test Strips: </b>These strips are readily available on the market, accessible at pharmacies or stores. The strip features a test window where you\'ll place the sample.\n<b>2. Collect the Sample: </b>As mentioned earlier, these strips detect the level of HCG hormone in urine. For optimal results, an early morning sample is recommended due to its higher hormone concentration. However, you can use samples at any time during the day. Collect urine in a clean and dry container.\n<b>3. Conduct the Test: </b>After collecting the urine sample, either apply it to the test window on the strip or place the strip in the urine sample. Some strips have a maximum line; ensure that your urine sample doesn\'t cross this line. Alternatively, you can insert the strip into your urine stream for testing.\n\n<i>Performing a pregnancy test at home using strips is a simple and reliable process when following these steps.</i></string>

    <string name="earlySigns"><b>Early Signs of Pregnancy:</b></string>
    <string name="missedPeriods">Missed Period</string>
    <string name="missedPC">A missed menstrual cycle is frequently the first obvious sign of pregnancy. During early pregnancy, some women may suffer moderate bleeding or spotting, which is known as implantation bleeding.\n\nMissed or late periods can occur for a variety of causes other than pregnancy. These can range from hormone problems to severe medical disorders. Furthermore, abnormalities are widespread during two stages of a woman\'s life: the onset of menstruation and the start of the menopausal transition.\n</string>
    <string name="morningSickness">Morning Sickness</string>
    <string name="morningC">Nausea and vomiting, generally referred to as morning sickness, can occur at any time of the day. It commonly begins around the sixth week of pregnancy due to hormonal changes. Though it\'s termed morning sickness, it can come at any moment.\n\nMorning sickness, a typical illness during pregnancy, comprises nausea and vomiting, primarily experienced during the early hours of the day. This syndrome is not restricted to mornings, as the name might suggest, and can occur at any time throughout the day. Typically, morning sickness starts about the sixth week of pregnancy, peaking during the eighth to twelfth weeks, however, it can vary among individuals.\n\nThe particular origin of morning sickness is not understood, however hormonal changes, especially the raised levels of human chorionic gonadotropin (hCG) and estrogen during pregnancy, are believed to have a significant impact. Additionally, elements including a heightened sense of smell, specific foods, fatigue, and emotional stress could contribute to the severity of symptoms.\n\nWhile morning sickness is generally considered a natural component of pregnancy, severe and chronic cases may lead to dehydration and weight loss, necessitating medical intervention. Managing morning sickness typically requires dietary modifications, such as taking small, frequent meals, staying hydrated, and avoiding triggers that worsen symptoms.\n\nIt\'s vital for pregnant individuals experiencing morning sickness to speak with healthcare providers to guarantee appropriate guidance and assistance throughout this phase. Understanding and treating morning sickness contributes to a more comfortable and healthier pregnancy journey.\n</string>
    <string name="breastChanges">Breast Changes</string>
    <string name="breastC">Breast changes are a natural part of a woman\'s life, impacted by a variety of variables including puberty, the menstrual cycle, pregnancy, and aging. These alterations may include variations in breast size, tenderness, and texture.\n\nDuring puberty, hormonal changes promote breast development, while the menstrual cycle can cause monthly differences. Pregnancy causes major changes that prepare the breasts for lactation. As a woman matures, her breasts may lose firmness and density.\n\nIt\'s important to note that, while most breast changes are normal, any sudden or unusual changes should be reviewed with a doctor. Regular self-exams and mammograms, when prescribed, help with early detection and management of any problems.\n\nUnderstanding the numerous elements that influence breast changes enables women to successfully navigate these transitions and prioritize breast health at different periods of life.\n</string>
    <string name="uniration">Frequent Urination</string>
    <string name="urinationC">Increased blood flow to the pelvic area and hormonal changes can lead to more frequent urination, especially during the early stages of pregnancy. The growing uterus places pressure on the bladder.\n\nFrequent urination is a typical occurrence that can be affected by a variety of factors such as hydration state, medical disorders, and lifestyle choices. It is frequently related to increased fluid consumption, especially water and caffeinated beverages.\n\nMedical diseases such as urinary tract infections (UTIs), diabetes, and prostate problems can all add to frequent urination. This symptom may appear during pregnancy as a result of bladder pressure.\n\nLifestyle decisions, such as excessive alcohol or caffeine usage, might worsen the problem. Anxiety or pharmaceutical side effects may also play a role.\n\nWhile occasional increased urination is normal, persistent or uncomfortable scenarios require treatment. Seeking advice from a healthcare professional can help uncover the underlying reason and develop suitable management techniques, assuring total well-being.</string>
    <string name="fatigue">Fatigue</string>
    <string name="fatigueC">The body experiences significant changes, including increased blood production and hormonal shifts, contributing to fatigue. This can be especially pronounced in the first trimester.\n\nFatigue is a common and often overlooked symptom that can come from various factors.\n\nPotential reasons for fatigue include insufficient sleep, worry, poor nutrition, and dehydration. Chronic conditions such as anemia, thyroid disorders, and sleep apnea can also add to chronic fatigue.\n\nAdditionally, living choices, such as a sedentary routine or excessive caffeine intake, may impact energy levels. Mental health conditions like depression and worry can appear as fatigue.\n\nWhile occasional fatigue is normal, persistent or severe cases deserve attention. Seeking guidance from a healthcare professional can help identify the underlying cause and guide appropriate management strategies, promoting overall well-being.</string>

    <string name="laterSigns"><b>Later Signs of Pregnancy:</b></string>
    <string name="appetite">Increased Appetite</string>
    <string name="appetiteC">Increased appetite is a common occurrence that can result from various factors, including hormonal changes, psychological factors, and changes in physical exercise.\n\nSome women experience a rise in appetite, while others may have aversions to certain foods. Cravings for specific foods are also common and can vary greatly Hormonal changes, such as those during puberty, pregnancy, or certain medical conditions, can influence appetite. Emotional factors like worry, boredom, or mood disorders may also lead to an increase in eating.\n\nPhysical activity levels can affect appetite, with increased exercise often linked with higher energy needs. Certain medications may also lead to changes in appetite.\n\nWhile occasional changes in appetite are normal, chronic or sudden increases may warrant attention. Consulting with a healthcare professional can help identify the underlying cause and decide suitable management strategies, promoting overall well-being.</string>
    <string name="mood_swing">Mood Swings</string>
    <string name="mood_swingC">Mood swings are defined by rapid and intense changes in emotional states, ranging from happiness and excitement to irritability or sadness. These fluctuations can be affected by various factors, including hormonal changes, stress, lack of sleep, and underlying mental health conditions.\n\nHormonal fluctuations can impact mood, leading to mental alterations. Expectant mothers may experience irritability, mood fluctuations, or heightened feelings.\nHormonal shifts during puberty, menstruation, pregnancy, and menopause can add to mood swings. Stressful scenarios, inadequate sleep, and certain medications may also play a role.\n\nMood swings are a natural part of the human experience, but persistent or extreme changes may indicate an underlying problem. Seeking support from friends, family, or mental health professionals can be beneficial in managing mood swings and improving general emotional well-being..</string>
    <string name="changesSkin">Changes in Skin</string>
    <string name="changesSkinC">Changes in the skin are a normal part of life and can be affected by various factors, including age, environmental factors, and underlying health conditions. These changes may manifest as alterations in texture, tone, and general appearance.\n\nPregnancy hormones can cause changes in the skin, including discoloration (chloasma) and the appearance of stretch lines. Proper skincare is important to managing these alterations.\n\nAs individuals age, the skin begins to lose some elasticity and moisture, leading to the development of wrinkles and fine lines. Exposure to environmental factors like sun, wind, and pollution can accelerate these changes.\nHormonal fluctuations during puberty, pregnancy, and menopause can also impact the face, causing conditions such as acne or increased sensitivity. Certain health conditions and lifestyle factors, such as smoking or poor nutrition, may add to skin changes.\n\nWhile some skin changes are inevitable, proper skin care, a healthy lifestyle, and protection from environmental factors can help reduce the effect. Consulting with dermatologists for prolonged or concerning changes ensures effective management and promotes overall skin health.</string>
    <string name="weightGain">Weight Gain</string>
    <string name="weightGainC">Weight gain is a common and multifaceted aspect affected by factors such as diet, physical exercise, metabolism, and underlying health conditions. It is a natural occurrence at different times of life.\n\nWeight gain is a natural feature of pregnancy to support the developing baby. A healthy weight gain is important for the well-being of both the mother and the infant. The recommended weight gain changes based on pre-pregnancy weight.\n\nChanges in diet, especially an excess of calorie consumption, can contribute to weight gain. A sedentary lifestyle, lacking regular physical exercise, also plays a role in the accumulation of excess weight. Hormonal changes, such as those during pregnancy or menopause, can influence body weight.\n\nCertain health conditions, medications, and genetic factors may lead to weight gain. Emotional factors like stress and mental health issues can also impact eating habits and, subsequently, body weight.\n\nWhile weight gain is a normal part of life, maintaining a balanced diet, engaging in regular physical exercise, and addressing underlying health problems are crucial for overall well-being. Consulting healthcare professionals for personalized advice ensures effective management and a healthy approach to weight.</string>
    <string name="babyMovement">Movement of the Baby</string>
    <string name="babyMovementC">The movement of the baby, also known as fetal movement, is an important aspect during pregnancy. It shows the well-being and development of the baby in the womb. Fetal movements are usually felt by the mother as early as the second trimester.\n\nInitially, the movements may be subtle flutters, changing into more pronounced kicks, rolls, and stretches as the pregnancy progresses. The pattern of fetal movement can vary, but a consistent pattern is usually observed.\n\nMonitoring fetal movements is important for assessing the baby\'s health. A sudden decrease in movement or a major change in the established pattern should be promptly reported to healthcare professionals. Regular check-ups, ultrasounds, and talks with healthcare providers contribute to ensuring a healthy and active baby during pregnancy.</string>
    <string name="Swelling">Swelling</string>
    <string name="SwellingC">Swelling, also known as edema, is the enlargement of body parts caused by a buildup of fluid. It can occur in different parts of the body, typically in the feet, ankles, and hands. Swelling may come from factors such as prolonged standing or sitting, pregnancy, hot weather, or an underlying medical problem.\n\nSome swelling, especially in the ankles and feet, is normal due to increased fluid retention.\n\nDuring pregnancy, hormonal changes and greater pressure on blood vessels can lead to swelling in the limbs. Preeclampsia, a pregnancy complication, can also cause significant swelling along with other symptoms and needs quick medical attention.\n\nWhile mild swelling is normal, sudden or severe swelling, especially if followed by other symptoms, should be quickly addressed. Elevating the impacted limbs, staying hydrated, and regular movement can help ease mild swelling. However, getting medical help is crucial for identifying and managing the underlying cause of persistent or concerning swelling.\n\nIt\'s crucial to remember that every woman\'s pregnancy journey is unique, and not all may experience the same symptoms. Consultation with a healthcare professional is advised for confirmation and personalized guidance.</string>


    <string name="salt">Pregnancy test using Salt</string>
    <string name="saltC">While there isn\'t a defined procedure or formal instructions for doing a salt pregnancy test, it commonly includes combining a tablespoon or two of salt with a sample of morning urine. The combination is then permitted to settle for a few minutes to a few hours. Some argue that if the solution turns "milky" or "cheesy," it implies pregnancy.\n\nHowever, it\'s vital to emphasize that this method lacks scientific validity and reliability. For accurate results, it\'s advised to utilize commercially available pregnancy tests designed to detect human chorionic gonadotropin (hCG) in urine. Always consult with healthcare specialists for reliable pregnancy confirmation and guidance.</string>
    <string name="sugar">Pregnancy test using Sugar</string>
    <string name="sugarC">There is no accurate and scientifically proven "sugar pregnancy test." While certain homemade pregnancy tests involve sugar, they lack reliability and may produce false results. For precise pregnancy testing, it is strongly advised to use widely available commercial pregnancy tests specifically designed to detect the presence of human chorionic gonadotropin (hCG) in urine. These tests undergo rigorous testing to ensure accuracy. Relying on unverified homemade tests may result in misleading outcomes and unnecessary confusion. Always consult with a healthcare professional for accurate pregnancy confirmation and expert guidance.</string>
    <string name="Vinegar">Pregnancy test using Vinegar</string>
    <string name="VinegarC">A vinegar pregnancy test is a homemade method often suggested for spotting pregnancy by combining white vinegar with a sample of urine. However, it\'s important to approach this method with caution as it lacks scientific validation and reliability.\n\n<b>Procedure:\n\n </b>• Collect a sample of morning pee in a clean container.\n• Add a small amount of white vinegar to the pee sample.\n• Observe the mixture for any changes, such as fizzing, popping, or other reactions.\n\n<b>Caution:</b>The vinegar pregnancy test is not scientifically proven and may give inaccurate results.Homemade tests, including the vinegar test, are not created or validated for pregnancy detection.False positives or negatives can occur, leading to confusion and possible stress.\n\n<b>Recommendation:</b> For reliable and accurate pregnancy testing, it\'s advisable to use commercially available pregnancy tests specifically made to detect human chorionic gonadotropin (hCG) in urine. These tests receive rigorous testing for accuracy and are a more dependable option. Always speak with healthcare professionals for precise pregnancy confirmation and advice.</string>
    <string name="shampoo">Pregnancy test using Shampoo</string>
    <string name="shampooC">A shampoo pregnancy test is a DIY method that involves combining a small amount of shampoo with a sample of urine to allegedly detect pregnancy. However, it\'s crucial to approach this method with care as it lacks scientific validation and reliability.\n\n<b>Procedure: </b>• Collect a sample of morning pee in a clean container.\n• Add a small amount of shampoo to the pee sample.\n• Mix the solution and watch for any changes, such as color alterations or formations.\n\n<b>Caution:</b> The shampoo pregnancy test is not scientifically proven and may give inaccurate results. Homemade tests, including the shampoo test, are not created or validated for pregnancy detection. False positives or negatives can occur, leading to confusion and possible stress.\n\n<b>Recommendation: </b>For reliable and accurate pregnancy testing, it\'s advisable to use commercially available pregnancy tests specifically made to detect human chorionic gonadotropin (hCG) in urine. These tests receive rigorous testing for accuracy and are a more dependable option. Always speak with healthcare professionals for precise pregnancy confirmation and advice.</string>
    <string name="wheat">Pregnancy test using Wheat and Barley</string>
    <string name="wheatC">There isn\'t a scientifically proven "wheat and barley pregnancy test." Some homemade pregnancy tests involve mixing wheat and barley seeds with urine, saying that a reaction indicates pregnancy. However, these methods lack consistency and may lead to unreliable results.\n\n<b>Procedure:</b>\n1. Collect a sample of morning pee in a clean container.\n2. Add a small amount of wheat and barley seeds to the pee sample.\n3. Observe the mixture for any changes, such as fizzing or reactions.\n\n<b>Caution:</b>\n- The wheat and barley pregnancy test is not supported by scientific evidence and may give inaccurate results.\n- Homemade tests are not designed or tested for pregnancy detection.\n- False positives or negatives can occur, causing confusion and needless stress.\n\n<b>Recommendation:</b> For accurate pregnancy testing, it is advisable to use commercially available pregnancy tests specifically made to detect human chorionic gonadotropin (hCG) in urine. These tests receive rigorous testing for reliability and are a more dependable option. Always consult healthcare professionals for precise pregnancy confirmation and advice.</string>
    <string name="soda">Pregnancy test using Baking Soda</string>
    <string name="sodaC">A baking soda pregnancy test is a DIY procedure that includes combining baking soda with a sample of urine to reportedly detect pregnancy. However, it\'s vital to approach this procedure with caution as it lacks scientific confirmation and reliability.\n\n<b>Procedure: </b>\n1. Collect a sample of morning urine in a clean container.\n2. Add a small amount of baking soda to the urine sample.\n3. Observe the mixture for any changes, such as fizzing or reactions.\n\n<b>Caution: </b>\n- The baking soda pregnancy test is not scientifically established and may yield erroneous results. - Homemade tests, including the baking soda test, are not created or validated for pregnancy detection.\n- False positives or negatives can occur, leading to confusion and potential stress.\n\n<b>Recommendation:</b> For dependable and accurate pregnancy testing, it\'s suggested to utilize commercially available pregnancy tests specifically developed to detect human chorionic gonadotropin (hCG) in urine. These tests undergo extensive testing for accuracy and are a more trusted option. Always seek healthcare professionals for precise pregnancy confirmation and advice.</string>

    <string name="disclaimerH"><b>⚠️ Disclaimer:</b></string>
    <string name="disclaimer"><b>Purpose:</b> The content provided in this app is for informational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always consult with a qualified healthcare provider regarding any medical concerns.\n<b>Individual Circumstances:</b> Individual circumstances may vary, and the information presented might not be suitable for everyone. It is essential to seek personalized advice from a healthcare professional based on your specific situation.\n<b>Endorsement and Effectiveness:</b> The authors and publishers do not endorse or guarantee the effectiveness of any medical treatments, therapies, or strategies mentioned in the article. Pregnant individuals should exercise caution and consult healthcare professionals before making any changes to their healthcare routine.\n<b>External Links:</b> Links to external websites are provided for additional information. We do not endorse or take responsibility for the content on these external sites and do not guarantee their accuracy.\n<b>Medical Emergencies:</b> In case of a medical emergency or urgent healthcare needs, seek immediate assistance from a qualified healthcare professional or your nearest medical facility.\n\nBy continuing, you acknowledge and <b><i>agree to these terms.</i></b>
    </string>
    <string name="disc"><b>Disclaimer of ZenMom</b>\n\n<i>Last Updated: 02-Apr-2024\n</i>Dear <b>ZenMom</b> Community,\n\nThank you for selecting <b>ZenMom</b> as your go-to resource during this incredible journey of pregnancy. Our commitment is to deliver accurate and reliable information, aligning with Google Play Content Policy for a secure and valuable user experience. Please take a moment to review the following content guidelines:\n\n<b>1. Content Sources:</b>\nZenMom features content curated from reputable and authoritative internet platforms, ensuring alignment with Google Play Content Policy standards.\n\n<b>2. Information Accuracy:</b>\nWhile we strive for accuracy, the dynamic nature of medical information mandates cross-referencing with professional healthcare advice. Consult your healthcare provider for personalized guidance.\n\n<b>3. External Links:</b>\nThe app may contain links to external websites for additional information. Users are encouraged to review the Privacy Policies and Terms of Use of these third-party sites, as we have no control over their content or practices, adhering to Google Play guidelines.\n\n<b>4. Credits to Reputable Sources:</b>\nWe express gratitude and credit reputable sources from which content is curated, following Google Play guidelines for transparency.\n\n[American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists (ACOG), National Health Service (UK), American Dental Association (ADA), Mayo Clinic, UCSF Health, Stanford Children\'s Health, American Pregnancy Association, Tommy\'s, Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), BMC Public Health Article, La Leche League International (LLLI), UNICEF DATA, National Institutes of Health,Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics, Food and Drug Administration (FDA), UChicago Medicine, Vaccinate Your Family]\n\n<b>5. Always Consult Your Healthcare Provider:</b>\nZenMom is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always consult your physician or qualified health provider for any medical inquiries, in accordance with Google Play standards.\n\n<b>6. Privacy Measures:</b>\nYour privacy is our utmost priority. Refer to our Privacy Policy for comprehensive details on how we handle your data, ensuring compliance with Google Play Content Policy.\n\nBy using <b>ZenMom</b> you acknowledge and wholeheartedly agree to the terms outlined in this content disclaimer, designed to meet Google Play standards. We are dedicated to providing you with a valuable and informed experience throughout your pregnancy journey.\n\nFor any questions or concerns, please feel free to reach out to us at contact.lamusoft@gmail.com, in accordance with Google Play guidelines.\n\nThank you for entrusting us with the privilege of accompanying you on your pregnancy journey.\n\nWarm regards,\n<b>LamuSoft Technology.</b>\n
    </string>
    <string name="continueBtn">Yes I understand. and Agree!</string>

    <string name="termsOfUse"><b>Welcome to BabyBliss!</b>\n\nThank you for choosing BabyBliss, the innovative mobile application developed by LamuSoft Team. Your journey through pregnancy with us is guided by the following terms and conditions, crafted to ensure a secure and enriching experience:\n\n<b>1. Acceptance of Terms:</b> By downloading, installing, or using BabyBliss, you agree to these terms and conditions. We encourage you to read and understand them thoroughly.\n\n<b>2. App Ownership and Usage Restrictions:</b> BabyBliss, including trademarks and intellectual property rights, belongs to LamuSoft Team exclusively. Unauthorized activities such as copying or modifying the app are strictly prohibited.\n\n<b>3. Changes to the App and Services:</b> We may make improvements or updates to enhance your experience with BabyBliss. Any changes or additional charges will be communicated clearly.\n\n<b>4. Data Security and Third-Party Services:</b> Your phone\'s security is essential. Please avoid jailbreaking or rooting, as it may affect the app\'s functionality. We integrate reputable third-party websites to provide additional information, but their privacy policies are beyond our control.\n\n<b>5. Internet Connection and Charges: </b>Certain features of BabyBliss require an active internet connection. You are responsible for any data charges imposed by your mobile network provider.\n\n<b>6. App Updates and Termination:</b> Stay updated with the latest app versions for optimal performance. We reserve the right to terminate the app at any time, without prior notice, for reasons including a breach of these terms.\n\n<b>7. Limitation of Liability:</b> We are not responsible for certain app functions. Please ensure your device is charged, and make informed decisions when relying on third-party information.\n\n<b>8. Updates to Terms and Conditions:</b> These terms and conditions may be updated periodically. We encourage you to review them regularly. Your continued use of BabyBliss after updates indicates acceptance of the modified terms.\n\n<b>Effective Date:</b> These terms and conditions are effective as of 02–04–24.\n\n<b>Contact Information:</b> For any inquiries or concerns about these terms and conditions, please contact us at <b>contact.lamusoft@gmail.com.</b>\n\nThank you for choosing BabyBliss. We are committed to providing you with a secure, informative, and joyful pregnancy journey!\n
    </string>

    <string name="aboutUs"><b>About Us:</b>\n\nWelcome to ZenMom! We are a dedicated team of developers and designers committed to supporting expecting mothers throughout their pregnancy journey. At ZenMom, we understand that pregnancy is a unique and transformative experience, and we\'re here to provide you with the tools, resources, and guidance you need to navigate it with confidence and ease.\n\n<b>Our Mission:</b>\n\nOur mission at ZenMom is to empower expecting mothers with personalized support, expert guidance, and reliable information throughout their pregnancy journey. We believe that every woman deserves access to comprehensive and user-friendly tools to help them make informed decisions about their health and the health of their baby.\n\n<b>What We Offer:</b>\n\n<b>Personalized Pregnancy Tracking:</b> Our app offers intuitive and easy-to-use pregnancy tracking tools that allow you to monitor your baby\'s growth and development, track important milestones, and stay informed about each stage of your pregnancy journey.\n<b>Expert Advice and Information:</b> Access a wealth of expert advice and information on various topics related to pregnancy, childbirth, and postpartum care. From nutrition and exercise to prenatal testing and labor preparation, we provide you with reliable information to help you make informed decisions about your health and well-being.\n<b>User-Friendly Interface:</b> We understand that pregnancy can be overwhelming, which is why we\'ve designed our app with a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to navigate and use. Whether you\'re a first-time mom or experienced parent, our app is designed to meet your needs and support you every step of the way.\n\n<b>Our Commitment:</b>\n\nAt ZenMom, we are committed to providing you with a safe, supportive, and inclusive space where you can track your pregnancy journey and get personalized diet tips and many guidelines. We are constantly working to improve and expand our app to better meet the needs of our users and ensure that every woman has access to the resources and support she needs to have a healthy and fulfilling pregnancy.\n\n<b>Connect With Us:</b>\n\nWe\'d love to hear from you! Whether you have feedback, questions, or suggestions for how we can improve our app, please don\'t hesitate to reach out to us at support@ZenMom.com. You can also connect with us on social media to stay up-to-date with the latest news and updates.\n\nThank you for choosing ZenMom as your trusted pregnancy companion. We\'re here to support you on your pregnancy journey and beyond!
    </string>

    ✤
    •
    <string name="pC">-by freepik</string>
    <string name="dropdownButtonDescription">This is Dropdown Button</string>
    <string name="dataSourceText">Data Source for Increase information reliability and Know more depth:</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="scrollViewDescription">This is an Scroll View</string>
    <string name="explore_baby_growth">Explore Baby Growth</string>
    <string name="expected_delivery_date">Expected delivery date: 27–09–24</string>
    <string name="highlight_w7">The embryo has a large forehead, and the eyes and ears continue to develop. The inner ears start to develop, but the outer ears on the sides of the head will not appear for a couple more weeks. The limb buds start to form cartilage, which will develop into the bones of the legs and arms.</string>
    <string name="explore_more">Explore More</string>
    <string name="popupInfoTitle">It is very important to track each milestone during your pregnancy.\nEnter information here (it\'s completely safe)</string>
    <string name="diet">Diet</string>
    <string name="tests">Tests</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="Me">Me</string>
    <string name="see_less">See Less</string>
    <string name="see_more">See More</string>
    <string name="week">Week</string>
    <string name="prenatal_nutrition_guide_description">Prenatal nutrition Guide description</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="days_to_go">Days to go</string>
    <string name="disclaimers">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="rate_us">Rate us</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="askForDateText">Enter the first day of your last period to calculate your due date</string>
    <string name="howToCalculate"><u>Why are we asking and how we calculate it?</u></string>

    <string name="get_started">Get Started!</string>
    <string name="enter_a_date">Select a Date</string>
    <string name="policyTxt"><u>Privacy Policy!</u></string>
    <string name="moreBtn">Setting</string>

</resources>